<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<document>
<webSite>http://demo.imb2b.com/</webSite>
<webMaster>kelvin-chu@trade-eye.com</webMaster>
<updatePeri>120</updatePeri>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[China International Hardware Show strikes again]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=240]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Asias premier event for the hardware industry  the China International Hardware Show (CIHS)  is returning to Shanghai, China this month. The three-day event opening on Sep 19 will feature 2,400 exhibi]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp;Asia&rsquo;s premier event for the hardware industry &ndash; the China International Hardware Show (CIHS) &ndash; is returning to Shanghai, China this month. The three-day event opening on Sep 19 will feature 2,400 exhibitors, including over 200 companies from about 20 countries and regions, and showcase 103,500 square-meters of products such as tools, building hardware, security locks and fittings as well as kitchen and bathroom wares and accessories.&nbsp;
&nbsp;
As in previous years, the comprehensive range of exhibits will be presented in a purpose-oriented and distinct format spotlighting the Protective Products zone, the Abrasives &amp; Grinding zone and accompanied by the debut of the Processing &amp; Manufacturing Equipment zone.
&nbsp;
Co-located with CIHS are another two highlights of the event - the China International Building Hardware Show and the China International Locks &amp; Security Show.
&nbsp;
Among all on display, 100 products with outstanding quality, innovation and design will be handpicked and honored at the &ldquo;Best of China&rdquo; showcase.
&nbsp;
International and regional group participation this year is particularly active with the Taiwan Pavilion taking the lead. Fronted once again by the Taiwan Hand Tools Manufacturers Association and supported by the Taichung City Government, the organizers have taken one step further by incorporating a Taichung industry themed hand tools specialty zone promoting Taiwan&rsquo;s image for high quality hand tools and raising its brand awareness to the international market, with Taichung&rsquo;s landmark &ndash; the Taichung Park Pavilion &ndash; and its iconic local delicacies &ldquo;sun biscuits&rdquo; and pineapple cakes to reflect the region&rsquo;s various industries and unique characteristics.
&nbsp;
In addition, in partnership with the Importers and Exporters Association of Taipei, CIHS will for the first time be hosting a business event for buyers to conduct one-to-one exchange with Taiwanese exhibitors and gain an in-depth understanding of their company, products and the Taiwanese hardware industry.
&nbsp;
Based on last year&rsquo;s figure and the slew of wide-ranging show offerings, organizers have projected a turnout of over 41,000 visitors.
&nbsp;
And it looks like they will not be disappointed.
&nbsp;
Currently, leading international sourcing houses and retail giants with confirmed participation include Lowe&rsquo;s Kingfisher, B&amp;Q, Walmart, Carrefour, Home Depot, LG Sourcing, Leroy Merlin, Saint-Gobain and Metro.
&nbsp;
On top of that, a buying delegation led by the European DIY Retail Association (EDRA) will be bringing more foreign heavyweights with the likes of Lowe&rsquo;s from the U.S., Sodimac from Chile&rsquo;s Falabella and Turkey&rsquo;s biggest retail chain, Tekzen to procure at the show.
&nbsp;
EDRA has 24 members from over 20 countries including the five major trade member states - Germany, Italy, France, Spain and Finland - with influence spanning 43 countries around the world.
&nbsp;
www.hardwareshow-china.com
&nbsp;
China International Hardware Show 2012
September 19-21, 2012
Shanghai New International Expo Centre
&nbsp;
# # #
&nbsp;
About China International Hardware Show
China International Hardware Show (CIHS) in Shanghai is Asia's largest trade fair for the entire hardware and DIY sectors offering specialist traders and buyers a comprehensive category of products and services ranging from Tools, DIY and Building Hardware to Security, Locks and Fittings. Increasingly, European and American exhibitors are using this show as their gateway to markets in Asia.
&nbsp;
&nbsp;
About the Organizers
Koelnmesse
As a world-renowned trade fair organizer, Koelnmesse has an excellent track record for organizing some of the world&rsquo;s most successful trade events, such as the accomplished International Hardware Fair and spoga+gafa in Cologne, Germany. With over 80 years&rsquo; experience in organizing large-scale commercial events connecting buyers and sellers, Koelnmesse brings forth an unrivaled skill-set and expertise needed to develop China International Hardware Show into one of the premier international trade shows in Asia.
www.koelnmesse.com
&nbsp;
China National Hardware Association
With almost 3,000 members, China National Hardware Association is made up of China&rsquo;s key hardware enterprises and professional associations. Its mission is to foster collaboration and communication between the government and enterprises, so as to build up China&rsquo;s hardware industry.
www.chinahardware.org.cn&nbsp;
&nbsp;]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201209/14/11-39-35-73-5276.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Industry News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2012-09-14 11:38</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Final Report of Asia Outdoor 2012]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=239]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[The 7th Asia Outdoor was successfully completed on July 29, breaking records once again. Altogether 570 exhibitors attended the show on a 48,000sqm fairground (2011: 570 exhibitors, 42,000sqm). Up to ]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[The 7th Asia Outdoor was successfully completed on July 29, breaking records once again. Altogether 570 exhibitors attended the show on a 48,000sqm fairground (2011: 570 exhibitors, 42,000sqm). Up to now, Asia Outdoor has grown to the thirdglobally biggest trade show in the outdoor industry. The 2nd Asia Bike as the first trade show on sports and luxury bikes in China, taking place in conjunction, occupied an area of 24,000 sqm and got 238 exhibitors. &nbsp;A steady increase is founded in the quantity of trade visitors, growing from 19,180 of 2011 to 20,542 of 2012. The trade visitors of Asia Bike 2012 reached 10,481.
&nbsp;
Outdoor insiders hope to observe the new trends of the Chinese outdoor market after a booming year in 2011 by attending the Asia Outdoor in Nanjing. With an enlarged scale of two additional halls, the fairground was still full of trade visitors, which indicates the show as vigorous as before and delights both show organizers and exhibitors. A representative of the well-known outdoor chains Sanfo said, &ldquo;The growth of the Chinese outdoor market is slowing down. The rate was 50% in 2011, and it is likely to drop to 20% this year. &rdquo; Mr. Jaeger, consultant of the two shows, said, &ldquo;There was a 20%-25% growth of the Chinese outdoor market in the first six months of 2012, which produces an unbelievable face from Europe in consideration of comparative figures with western ones.&rdquo;
&nbsp;
The trend towards lightweight outdoor products in the Chinese outdoor market is increasingly obvious. Strong increases also record the camping market. Tents exhibitors like the Japanese brand Logos and local brand Kingcamp have attended Asia Outdoor for a successive two years. &ldquo;This year the great show exceeded all my expectations and for 2013 we plan a larger area of our booth.&rdquo; said Mr. Shibata of the CEO of Logos from Osaka.
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;
Currently, on the other hand, the growth of the mountaineering equipment does not keep the same pace. As Mr. Zhong, General Manager of Kailas (a leading brand of mountaineering) said, &ldquo;Compared with other outdoor products, promotion of mountaineering equipment is in more need of support and interaction to interpret the meaning of outdoor sports.&rdquo;
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;
The suppliers of highly functional materials and accessories from Taiwan and Japan also participated the show with great passion. &ldquo;Asia Outdoor has become the top platform for the national and international OEM and Sourcing.&rdquo;, said Richard Li, the project director of Asia Outdoor.
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;
Forums and workshops of Asia Outdoor 2012 make great contributions to the industry and gain much concern. The lecture of Hilke fromEOG Working Groupfoundthe greatest attention to the topic&quot;Sustainability&quot; .COA (China Outdoor Alliance) organized by the 5 leading Chinese brands (namely Toread, Kailas, Northland, Mobi Garden and Scaler) together with Asia Outdoor, makes &quot;Sustainability&quot; a topicin the working group.
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;
The 8th Asia Outdoor will take place at Nanjing International Expo Center from July 25 to 28, 2013.
&nbsp;]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Industry News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2012-08-01 17:23</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Final report of Asia Bike 2012]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=238]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[The 2nd Asia Bike was held in Nanjing from July 26 to 29. Altogether 238 exhibitors from 14 countries distributed on the 24,000 sqm fairground (2011 138 exhibitors, 12,000 sqm), attracted 10,481 trade]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[The 2nd Asia Bike was held in Nanjing from July 26 to 29. Altogether 238 exhibitors from 14 countries distributed on the 24,000 sqm fairground (2011 138 exhibitors, 12,000 sqm), attracted 10,481 trade visitors during the four-day exhibition period and 3751 bike fans on the two public days. 337 journalists from 147 media came for the show.
&nbsp;
The appointment for the third Asia Bike has been confirmed, at Nanjing International Expo Center from Sept. 19 to 22.
&nbsp;
As a &ldquo;small EUROBIKE&rdquo;, Asia Bike is the first trade show focused on sports and luxury bikes, cycling clothes and accessories in China.
&nbsp;
We get very good exhibitors and visitors this year.&rdquo; said Mr. Jaeger, the consultant of Asia Bike.
&nbsp;
Exhibitors from 14 nations came for the show and displayed the leading brands of sports and luxury bikes.
&nbsp;
Show in the Show&rdquo; program represents the most sporting and the most expensive bicycles, and becomes a magnet for visitors and media. Among all the highlights in this region, a number of unique bicycles feast on your eyes, such as Tour de France Winner Pinarello, BMC, Specialized, Time, Bergamont, Focus, Corratec, Pedelecs of Smart, foldable King Ludwig Rad from Bavaria. The Pearson bike from New Zealand ranked the first place, at a steep price of about 280,000 RMB or 35,000 euros with delivery time of one to two years.
&nbsp;
The forum and workshops of Asia Bike 2012 went very well and attracted a lot of audience.
&nbsp;
Test Center is extremely popular among visitors. Two separate tracks were designed this year a natural track for Mountain bikes and a test course for Road bikes and E-bikes.The Fashion show and the Endurance Cycling Race are also very attractive and fascinating.
&nbsp;
Here are some comments from the exhibitors
&nbsp;
Helen Li of LOOK Asia Bike has come to an adequate form and gives the industry a good platform. The quality of the visitors was excellent. Also rush about The manufacturers have invested much in the quality of stands.
&nbsp;
Bernd Lesch of Shark bike in Germany we were very successful and gained many new dealers. We plan to attend Asia Bike 2013 with a greater stand.&nbsp;
&nbsp;
Dennis Chan, Iron Ore from Hong Kong (agent of BMC, cervelo, Times, yeti, Fox, etc.) Asia Bike exactly fulfills our requirements and the growing marketing needs for high-end bikes in China. In this form, Asia Bike has a great future.
&nbsp;
Masaki Miyaki, vice-president of Shimano We are very satisfied with the positive development of Asia Bike. Our customers declared themselves very content.
&nbsp;
Ian Hsieh, of Corratec The quality of the stands and the visitors were all very good.
&nbsp;
Tony Wu, of UCC We are very pleased to meet so many foreign bike brands here. This is a strong motivation for Chinese manufacturers. That Asia Bike changes its event time to September next year gives us greater chance to show the CHANGE of our new collection.
&nbsp;
Sicong Liu, of Daimler Smart The presentation of the Smart E-bike together with our E-Smart is very successful.&nbsp;
&nbsp;
Maik Geletneky, of Bergamont Good show, good dealer, good conversations.
&nbsp;
Messe Friedrichshafen will continue to back up the shows, offer the greatest support by EUROBIKE transfers.
&nbsp;
We are really looking forward to our new appointment of the third Asia Bike Sept. 19-22, 2013.]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Industry News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2012-08-01 16:53</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Small Drops –– Overall Export Turnover of the Taiwan Sporting Goods decrease by 3%]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=237]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ For the first nine months of 2011, the total export value of Taiwan export value of Taiwan sporting goods reached TWD 25,116,677,000 according to export statistics. With a small drop by 4% compared t]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; For the first nine months of 2011, the total export value of Taiwan export value of Taiwan sporting goods reached TWD 25,116,677,000 according to export statistics. With a small drop by 4% compared to the same period in the previous year. Among all the listed sporting goods categories, articles and equipment for general physical exercise, gymnastics or athletic remains taking the top ranking as in 2010 with an impressive export value of TWD 12,636,948,000; slightly grow compared with the value in 2010(TWD 12,587,263,000). Other golf equipment took the second place with the value of TWD 3,554,807,000, decreasing by 11% compared to the same period in last year. The third category is sunglasses with the value of TWD 1,989,701,000.
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Despite the fact that overall market decreased slightly compared to the same period in last year, some categories still obtained significant growth. Those are men's or boys' swimwear of other textile materials, ski suits of other textile materials, sailboards, golf clubs, complete, volleyballs, and fish-hooks whether or not smelled. The values of above-mentioned categories grew by 95% and more. Among them, ski suits, of other textile materials stood at TWD 5,045,000, enjoyed the highest growth rate 3379%.
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Export value of ski suits of man-made fibers, other camping goods, of other textile materials, tables for table-tennis, table-tennis bats (paddles), and table-tennis balls do not look very well in this year since they met with a decline by over 40%. 
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Generally, the export performance for Taiwan sporting goods in 2011 does not face severe drops. However, US and the European markets are predicted to meet with greater depression than in this year, while emerging countries such as Brazilian market is expected to be more optimistic compared to US and the European markets. Companies in Taiwan need to take necessary precaution; in order to be outstanding on global market continuously, Taiwan sporting goods industry ought to endeavor to develop innovative products. In addition to product innovation, extra attention needs to be paid to international market trends to enable Taiwan industry keeping path with the whole world.





]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Sports Supplier News ]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2012-01-19 16:04</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Sport= Health = energy = confidence = Happiness]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=235]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[       The development of sport industry can promote peoples health and safe, while it also can contribute to the overall economic development. Sport industry has become one of the new economic drivin]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; The development of sport industry can promote people&rsquo;s health and safe, while it also can contribute to the overall economic development. Sport industry has become one of the new economic driving forces in major developed countries. In addition, it can increase the quality of life and promote the physical and mental health. Thus, the development of sport industry is an important step in the overall country development.
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; In the past fifty years, Taiwan's sport industry, relying on supports and promotion of government departments and efforts of predecessors, has accumulated a wealth of manufacturing, R &amp; D and market development experience, and produced products that recognized by consumers around the world.
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Under the funding and guides of several government departments, the exportation quantity of various sport goods set records repeatedly. Products such as rackets, running shoes, golf kit, skating shoes, outdoor goods, bicycles, and fitness equipments etc., are all have huge market shares. 
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; In the aspect of the domestic market, Taiwan government promotes sports policies which emphasize the importance of competitive sports and of participative sports in the past ten years. In addition to striving to get opportunities for hosting international sport events, the related government departments devoted to building cycling roads and regional sports centers, and repairing swimming pool, in order to promote &ldquo;Sport For All&rdquo;, which let everyone can exercise anytime and everywhere. They also make effort to strengthen the close relationship between industry, government, and the academic community. In addition, the National Sports Council has drawn up &ldquo;The Bill of Award for the Development of Sport Industry (draft)&rdquo; in 2010. This bill, if passed, will make a positive impact on Taiwan&rsquo;s sport industry: it can promote flourishing development of industries, and thus reduce unemployment rate, decrease medical expenses, and improve our quality of life.
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Taipei Sporting Goods Association has been established for 38 years since 1973, and now is run by the 13th committee board. We acknowledge with gratitude the valuable contributions and efforts made by the former chairmen, directors, supervisors, and leaders of industry. Facing current net generation and rapidly changing social environment, we need to upgrade ourselves constantly. Looking forward to the future, the demand for sport equipments will continuously increase, and we surely would keep playing the bridge role for both buyers and sellers, corporately promoting prosperity of the industry, and striding toward next golden decade of sport industry.
&nbsp;
&nbsp;
Taipei Sporting Goods Association
Chairman Tom Chen]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Sports Supplier News ]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2012-01-19 16:00</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[New Perspectives of Taiwan's Sporting Goods]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=234]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[        As incomes rise around the world, more and more people are starting to pay more attention to preventative care and daily exercise. In addition to helping people lose weight, exercise can also ]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp;
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; As incomes rise around the world, more and more people are starting to pay more attention to preventative care and daily exercise. In addition to helping people lose weight, exercise can also reduce the incidence of cardiovascular disease, prevent cancer and stave off diabetes. Other positive benefits include suppressing negative emotions and raising life satisfaction. The promotion of exercise and health concepts among people has changed consumer behavior. In addition, health care awareness is increasing due to smaller families and graying societies. The industry must use product innovation and R&amp;D to raise living quality and satisfy other various needs to widely develop the green exercise industry and tap in the endless business opportunities for sporting goods. The European and American debt crisis are again impacting economies around the world. As economic gloom spreads around the globe, economists are predicting that world economic growth will slow and a second economic recession will occur. This will definitely further weaken the spending power of consumers and have a major impact on consumer product industries. According to statistics, our country&rsquo;s total sporting goods (Jan. to Aug. 2011) exports are estimated to be about US$975 million which represented a 5.96% increase of the exports over the same period in 2010. Though exports did not decrease in 2011, the industry is still being affected by global exchange rates, international oil prices and rising raw material prices. In order to maintain their competitive advantage in the sporting goods industry, companies must utilize the extensive manufacturing experience and knowledge management that they have accumulated over the years. As for exercise products, fitness equipment still leads the pack, posting an increase of 12.94%. In addition, golf equipment sets grew by 250% over 2010. This data shows that consumers are still attracted to high quality products. Other items including tennis racquets, skates and ball equipment saw modest growth and fitness products are currently going through a process of reshuffling.
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Due to the government&rsquo;s recent promotion of the industry clustering effect, Taiwan Sporting Goods Manufacturers Association (TSMA) together with the leading fitness equipment manufacturers, e.g. JOHNSON, TONIC, DYACO, HEALTH STREAM, SOLID FOCUS, DIRECTION, YA CHENG, CHI HUA, KING-I, J-STAR, GEOTUN and SUNRISE etc. established Taiwan S-Team Elite League (S-Team: S means Sports). They are now working together and continue to upgrade R&amp;D and design capabilities, mass production capacity for high-tech processes and raise OEM/ODM brand image &amp; recognition. It is hoped that that we have signed to upgrade S-Team as a global top class R&amp;D and manufacturing center which can make use of international division of labor and establish a sales and manufacturing logistics center to raise international competitiveness, After our government signed ECFA with China, Made in Taiwan is already having a major effect in markets. MIT has become a symbol for exceptional quality which is the most important advantage the industry can have. As the government creates a brand new playing field, concrete results have been seen in industry upgrading efforts. Through the promotion of Strengthen the Economy, Connect with the Asian-Pacific Region and Adopt a Global Outlook strategy, we can create more advantageous conditions for Taiwan&rsquo;s economy which will let companies join forces to develop the sporting goods industry.
&nbsp;
Taiwan Sporting&nbsp; Goods Manufactures Association
President&nbsp; Catherine Wang]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Sports Supplier News ]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2012-01-19 15:51</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[AQUARAMA 2011 ENJOYS ‘QUALITY’ SUCCESS]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=233]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[In the words of Dr. Alex Ploeg, Secretary General of Ornamental Fish International, Participating in Aquarama every two years is like coming home to meet long-time friends and business partners. ]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[In the words of Dr. Alex Ploeg, Secretary General of Ornamental Fish International, 
&ldquo;Participating in Aquarama every two years is like coming home to meet long-time 
friends and business partners. Aquarama 2011 was a&nbsp; very successful meeting of the 
industry&hellip;good for business and good for contacts.&rdquo; For Malaysian exhibitor, Bukit 
Merah Aquaculture, Aquarama 2011 (26-29 May, Suntec Singapore) was &ldquo;an excellent 
show&rdquo;, while first-time exhibitor, Doshe Aquaristik, from Germany, &ldquo;was very 
impressed with this exhibition&rdquo;, and Philippine company, Animalia 2000 Ichiban Inc., 
felt it was &ldquo;a fantastic show&rdquo;. 
&nbsp;
These sentiments were echoed by many of those who attended this year&rsquo;s glittering 
event. The organisers were encouraged by the fact that, despite the still-deep economic 
crisis affecting many countries and regions where substantial numbers of traditional 
attendees and exhibitors are based, Aquarama 2011 still pulled in the international 
trade from all corners of the globe. No fewer than 23 countries were represented 
among the exhibitors, while trade visitors came from an impressive total of 73 
countries. 
&nbsp;
Just as in 2009, there was a &lsquo;good-feel&rsquo; factor among the exhibitors, who maintained 
that the quality of the visitors and their genuine interest in doing business, more than 
made up for the more modest attendance figures. In&nbsp; their words, quality is always 
worth more than quantity.&nbsp;

    
        
            
            
        
    

&nbsp;
Were this not to be the case, there&rsquo;s no way that around 55% of this year&rsquo;s exhibitors 
would have either already signed contracts for 2013, or taken options to do so. Equally, 
if the level of business had not matched expectations, no company in its right mind 
would reserve a larger booth for 2013, as some important exhibitors have already done. Aquarama is, of course, much more than just a wide-ranging display of virtually every 
aquatic product you can think of. It&nbsp; is this, of course (and impressively so), but it also 
includes an unparalleled International Fish Competition, which this year received a 
staggering 1,355 entries, three brand new competitive elements, including a Freshwater 
nano Tank Competition, a free trade seminar programme consisting of three sessions 
and presented by top international speakers (deemed by many to be the best-ever 
staged at Aquarama), a fully subscribed Fish Farm Visit&hellip;and much else besides. 
&nbsp;
In the end, the organisers were justifiably pleased with the results. As Michiel Kruse, 
Managing Director of UBM Asia Singapore commented, &ldquo;Organising an event as 
complex and important for the industry as Aquarama,&nbsp; always presents a stiff 
challenge. We are therefore delighted that the efforts of our hardworking team and the 
invaluable and unflinching support of the industry, has made it possible for us to stage 
an event worthy of the name &lsquo;Aquarama&rsquo;, especially at such a difficult time in world 
economics.&rdquo; 
&nbsp;
To access further details of Aquarama 2011, and see a selection of this year&rsquo;s 
photographs, visit the show&rsquo;s website (www.aquarama.com.sg).&nbsp; For details and 
reservations relating to Aquarama 2013, please contact Doris Woo, Sales Manager at 
doris.woo@ubm.com or Adeline Chang, Project Executive at Adeline.chang@ubm.com&nbsp;&nbsp;
&nbsp;

    
        
            
            
            
        
    


UBM ASIA TRADE FAIRS PTE LTD 
No. 3 Pickering Street, #02-48 
China Square Central 
Singapore 048660&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 
Tel: +65 6592 0889 
Fax: +65 6438 6090&nbsp;
&nbsp;
&nbsp;
Aquarama 2013 will be held at Suntec, Singapore 
30 May &ndash; 2 June 2013&nbsp;
&nbsp;
]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201112/06/13-31-14-18-14.gif]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[Aquarama|PET|Sinagpore]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Industry News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[UBM ASIA TRADE FAIRS PTE LTD ]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-11-06 13:27</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Acewell Manufactures Top Quality Motorcycles and ATV Meters]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=232]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Established in 2003, Acewell started out as a company engaged in the design, manufacture and marketing of ATV and motorcycle meters. Their present markets are the motorcycle after-market and ATV origi]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp;Established in 2003, Acewell started out as a company engaged in the design, manufacture and marketing of ATV and motorcycle meters. Their present markets are the motorcycle after-market and ATV original manufacturers. In addition to ATV and motorcycle meters and turn signal lamps, the company also makes industrial control products for Echowell, LED tail lights for bicycles and recreational HID lamps.
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; Acewell&rsquo;s major products are motorcycle and ATV meters. Turn signal lamps are a new developed product by the company. Their major advantage is their electromechanical integration capability which enables Acewell to develop products that have higher stability and better water and vibration resistance properties than other products on the market. To expand their product range, the company regularly introduces new products on the market. During the R&amp;D process, innovation is emphasized. Everything from the water-proof construction and to electrical circuit design is totally new. The meter housing is made from forged and CNC machined aluminum alloy to provide extensive water proofing. Up to now, the company offers over 15 types of speed sensors including a hall-effect speed sensor. Their sensor structure and circuitry are brand-new, industry-leading designs.&nbsp;
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; Having already received ISO9001: 2000 quality system certification, Acewell is now introducing ISO/TS-16949 and plans to receive certification at the end of June 2010. With regard to their products, their motorcycle meters have all earned E-mark certification and the hall-effect sensor and HID lamp structural designs have been awarded patents. The company exports about 60% of their products mainly to Europe, America, Japan and Australia and sales have risen steadily over the years. In 2010, sales grew 15% over 2009. Looking towards the future, Acewell plans to further develop and expand their range of electrical parts and components for motorcycles and ATVs.]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201111/02/17-18-11-87-15.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Motorcycle Supplier News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[Infotrade  translation]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[William Hoyle ]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-11-02 17:17</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[BORN TO MAKE HISTORY]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=231]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Look at your loudspeakers and think of the outcome of treating them with acid rain during a sandstorm in intense sun. What are the chances that your audio system would survive under these harsh terms?]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp;Look at your loudspeakers and think of the outcome of treating them with acid rain during a sandstorm in intense sun. What are the chances that your audio system would survive under these harsh terms? However, Greness, a well reputated Taiwanese company in audio system designing, could provide just the right loudspeakers for your mobile vehicle that are resistant to rain drops and sun burns on road.
&nbsp;
By/ Greness Enterprise Co., Ltd.
&nbsp;
As company&rsquo;s latest invention, in 2010, Greness developed a series of designs featuring innovative mini-MP3 audio housings and their matching amplifier systems. This range has been instantly successful on the market due to its compatibility with Apple products (iPod, iPhone), regular MP3 players, CD players and radios, combined with superior sound quality. The series have been particularly popular in motorbikes, ATV, snowmobiles and other powersport vehicles which require weather- and water-resistance.
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; The history of Greness dates back to the 1980s. Until then, the market of waterproof loudspeakers has been very limited and designs were dated. This relative stagnation has been changed in 1989 when Greness was founded. The first major product line, including both marine waterproof loudspeakers and radio housings, has been tremendously successful and allowed the
Taiwanese company to rapidly build an outstanding reputation by introducing rare and distinctive products, available to both consumer and professional markets.&nbsp;
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; The company's reputation has been improved even further in 1995, when Greness set up its first factory in Taichung City in Taiwan. This step has allowed the company to introduce a wider array of popular products. In 2001, Greness started the production of public address systems with stunning audio quality, and continued to innovate its existing product range. Loudspeakers manufactured by the company were eventually designed to provide weather-proof, dust-proof, saltwater-proof, chlorine-proof, anti-UV, anti-humidity, anti-acid, anti-alkali and chemical resistance functions making them truly unique products, of quality superior to the competition.&nbsp;
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; At present, Greness&rsquo; product range covers marine and outdoor speakers, water-proof speakers for SPAs and public address speakers, with related accessories. Being available to both OEM and ODM clients, Greness products are used in a variety of environments, such as swimming pools, saunas, SPAs, boats, cruiseliners, vehicles and laboratories, many of which require &lsquo;heavy-duty&rsquo; features as well as churches, outdoor venues and gardens.
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; Having clients from all over the world, Greness continues to improve their current products and develop new designs to meet the needs of the customers. With the products and raw materials certified by internationally recognised certifying bodies, Greness only provides products of the highest quality possible and has established itself as a clear leader within its field. It is time to making history in a new world full of audio entertaining experiences.
&nbsp;]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201111/01/17-22-59-48-282.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Motorcycle Supplier News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-11-01 17:21</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Luxurious quality at a affordable price!]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=230]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[    Established in 2009, I-Greatest Rubber Ind. Co., Ltd. is located in Changhua County, Taiwan and specializes in the manufacture of high quality tires. At present, the company primarily manufactures]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Established in 2009, I-Greatest Rubber Ind. Co., Ltd. is located in Changhua County, Taiwan and specializes in the manufacture of high quality tires. At present, the company primarily manufactures motorcycle tires. Due to their reputation for stable quality, safety, comfort and durability, I-Greatest Rubber has gradually earned the recognition and trust of both domestic and international customers in the intensely competitive scooter market. As customer confidence and appreciation grew over time, their products gradually spread to each corner of Taiwan and found markets in many countries overseas that has made I-Greatest Rubber a shining beacon in Taiwan&rsquo;s tire industry.&nbsp;
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; I-Greatest Rubber uses advanced machinery and the latest work processes at its production facilities. In order to achieve exceptionable and stable quality, the company spared no expense to introduce Monsanto and Instron inspection and testing equipment (the inspection and testing equipment brands used by major international manufacturers) to give consumers a greater sense of security when using company products. In addition, I-Greatest Rubber has gotten involved in competitive scooter racing in order to give riders more stable handling and greater sensitivity in high speed turns during highly intense races. Besides enjoying the competitive thrill of racing, racers also feel safe and secure when vying to become champions. &nbsp;
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; I-Greatest Rubber was born out of the turmoil of the financial tsunami which makes the company even more appreciative and grateful. Under the leadership of President Hsiao and group of master engineers with decades of experience, the company aims to give consumers a higher level of experience and enjoyment from company products. Through our highly visible quality, the company creates unassuming luxury. By winning numerous championships and offering outstanding quality products that earn high C/P numbers is customer surveys, I-Greatest Rubber not only displays the business philosophy of the company helmsman but also reflects the strong customer orientation that was adopted when the company was founded.&nbsp;
I-Greatest Rubber business philosophy is very down to earth but it is also our vision.
&nbsp;]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201110/31/17-14-24-45-15.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Motorcycle Supplier News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[I-Greatest Rubber Ind. Co., Ltd.   ]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[William Hoyle]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-10-31 17:12</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Beautiful, Light, and with a Kick]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=229]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[   Studies have shown that shedding one kilogram of weight on vehicle wheels is about the same as taking ten kilograms off the vehicle body. It has the benefit of reducing petrol consumption and carbo]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;Studies have shown that shedding one kilogram of weight on vehicle wheels is about the same as taking ten kilograms off the vehicle body. It has the benefit of reducing petrol consumption and carbon emissions.
Forged aluminum wheels such as the ones recently launched by Taiwan&rsquo;s Wukawa are regarded by many enthusiasts as the epitome of performance. The wheels are light in weight, beautifully designed, and masterfully crafted.
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; The forging manufacturing process allows the light metal, aluminum, to become extremely tough. This unique quality enables sleeker designs and leads to better performance.&nbsp;
Wukawa's forged wheels are specifically designed for Japanese motorcycles. They weigh just 2.8kg for the front and 4.8kg for the back. The products are certified by the U.S. DOT and Japanese JWL safety standards.]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Motorcycle Supplier News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[Wukawa Industry Co., Ltd.]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-10-28 17:48</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Welcome to king yuchang]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=228]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Welcome to king yuchangOur Products in Your Life to be a world class excellent companyAt King Yuchang, we can manufacture the metal components you seekWe meet diverse buyer needs    At King Yuchang, w]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[Welcome to king yuchang
Our Products in Your Life to be a world class excellent company
At King Yuchang, we can manufacture the metal components you seek

&nbsp;
&nbsp;
We meet diverse buyer needs&nbsp;
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; At &nbsp;King Yuchang, we can manufacture the metal components you seek. How can we be so sure? Because we've been meeting the diverse needs of quality-focused buyers throughout the US, Europe, Asia and other markets for 17 years. These clients are satisfied with over 99.9 percent of the goods we ship. That's quite a lot considering our annual revenue is over $12 million.&nbsp;
&nbsp;
Using machines from Star, Tsugami and Miyano
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; So what is it about our products that impresses our clients? One reason is precision. Thanks to our utilization of CNC lathes and Swiss-type compound machines from Star, Tsugami and Miyano, we can make parts with greater accuracy than makers who employ lower-grade equipment. For another, we can fashion components for a range of finished goods &mdash; cars, motorcycles, electronics, lawn and garden accessories, furniture, firearms and more. Finally, we offer 20 new items yearly, with OEM/ODM customizations available on request.&nbsp;
&nbsp;
In-house Taiwan production
In our 5,000-square-meter Taiwan factory, we carry out all stages of production for rapid lead times. We have strong R&amp;D and QC teams. Our minimum order size is 5,000 units, and samples ship within one week, so call us today.
&nbsp;]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Motorcycle Supplier News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[King Yuchang Co., Ltd. ]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-10-27 16:53</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Intense Market Competition Leads to a 2.04% Reduction in Jan~Jul, 2011 Taiwan Motorcycle Exports]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=227]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[   According to statistics from Taiwans Directorate General of Customs, exports of Taiwan motorcycles for the first 7 months of 2011 were 222,409 units which represented a decrease of 2.04% over the p]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;According to statistics from Taiwan&rsquo;s Directorate General of Customs, exports of Taiwan motorcycles for the first 7 months of 2011 were 222,409 units which represented a decrease of 2.04% over the previous year. The total export amount was NT$8,643.555 which was 7.66% less than the same period last year. Looking over this period, the best export performance out of the top 20 countries was Japan which received NT$3,001,100 dollars in Taiwan motorcycle exports. Spain ranked second with NT$675,953 and the Italy occupied third place with NT$675,495. Out of the top 20 countries, Europe had the highest number with ten countries on the list and Asia had five.&nbsp;
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; As for growth rate, exports to Iraq grew by 159.73% making it the fastest growing export market for the first 7 months of 2011. The rapid growth in this market catapulted the country into the top 17 countries for Taiwan motorcycle exports. The second highest growth rate was in United States with 126.12%, followed by Colombia which took third place at 80.23%. Companies should watch how these markets continue to develop. Sales in the Italy declined by 68.21%. For two consecutive years, the decline exceeded 50%. The serious declines seen in this market is worth taking notice.&nbsp;
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; Though Taiwan motorcycle exports are still dropping, the level of the decline has shrunk considerably. In several European markets, growth has rebounded strongly to levels before the declines occurred. A few South American countries have also entered the top 20 list which shows the global economy is starting to recover. Taiwan companies are now seeing results in those overseas markets that they have been working hard to develop. In addition, the government&rsquo;s active promotion of electric scooters and trade-in subsidies has created an outstanding environment for development. This is positive news for the future of the industry. By further refining quality and efficiency and take advantage of strong government support, Taiwan motorcycle products can take a leading position in highly competitive global gas-powered and electrical vehicle markets and boost Taiwan&rsquo;s motorcycle industry to brand new heights.&nbsp;

]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201110/26/17-26-06-78-668.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Motorcycle Supplier News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[INFOTRADE]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-10-26 17:19</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Dedicated to Innovation and R&D  V-GRIP Chen Whua Products Sell Fast in U.S. and Europe Markets]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=226]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[V-GRIP Chen Whua Industry Co.,Ltd. started to develop parts and components for bicycles and motorcycles over 30 years ago and has established a excellent reputation in international markets. Now, the ]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp;
V-GRIP Chen Whua Industry Co.,Ltd. started to develop parts and components for bicycles and motorcycles over 30 years ago and has established a excellent reputation in international markets. Now, the company offers a mature line of motorcycle and bicycle parts to customers around the world.&nbsp;
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; V-GRIP Chen Whua parts are mostly made from plastic and rubber materials. Their mainstay products are grips, chainguards and fenders for motorcycles and bicycles. In addition to plastic and rubber materials, aluminum alloy and other materials are also incorporated into their products. Rigorous quality testing such as cold and heat resistance testing enable the company to manufacture a diverse range of fine quality and comfortably textured grip styles with anti-perspiration and anti-slip properties. In order to improve grip safety and meet the assembly requirements of the after market, Chen Whua extended the grip function by developing the lock grip which can be conveniently assembled by the user with just screws. For users who live in cold climates in the U.S. and Europe, the company has developed heated grips to provide extra comfort.
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; The business mission of V-GRIP Chen Whua is to embrace an innovative spirit in the research and development of new products. For their plastic products, V-GRIP&rsquo;s outstanding R&amp;D team is confident the company can satisfy each and every type of requirement. Over the past thirty years, the company has developed stable cooperative relations with many customers and their products are exported worldwide to Europe, the U.S. and Japan. Products are guaranteed to conform to standards and regulations so they can be used on heavy and regular motorcycles. V-GRIP Chen Whua also pay close attention to evolving market preferences. Different styles and designs are created for individual countries to conform to a diverse range of customer requirements. In addition to focusing on grip production, the company also offers peripheral products including motorcycle cleaning sets and rear view mirrors.
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; The objective of V-GRIP Chen Whua is to manufacture high quality, innovative products and this has become a competitive advantage of the company. Over the past three years, their V-GRIP brand has been introduced into the marketplace. In addition to existing OEM amd ODM, the company has also engaged in OBM brand design so more people around the world have the chance to use exceptional &lsquo;Made in Taiwan&rsquo; products.]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201110/25/15-19-31-72-15.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Motorcycle Supplier News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[Infotrade ]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[William Hoyle]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-10-25 15:14</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Investing in the World’s Green]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=225]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Florplant, Ornamental Plants and Landscaping Exhibition will be organized in Antalya, Turkey during 28th September -1st October 2011. The theme of the Exhibition is “Investing in the World’s Green”]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[Florplant, Ornamental Plants and Landscaping Exhibition will be organized in Antalya, Turkey during 28th September -1st October 2011. The theme of the Exhibition is “Investing in the World’s Green”. We conducted an interview with the General Manager of the Organizer company Mr. Mehmet DUKKANCI and asked him about the exhibition.
Mr. Dukkanci,what is the aim of the New Exhibition Florplant? Why it is organized in Antalya, Turkey?
Antalya is getting prepared for the World Botanic Expo in 2016. 900 acres of a giant garden, a landscaping area will be built in Antalya that is preparing to host the World Botanic Expo in 2016.
 It is expected that 90 countries will build their national gardens that will be visited during the 6 months of the exhibition by 10 million tourists.
These national gardens will be built with the support of the Turkish Garden &amp; Landscape design and implementation companies. Most of the basic supplies will be purchased from the local supliers. Thus our initial aim was to create an international environment that these service and supply providers would show up and try to get the business that is going to be created due to the Antalya Expo 2016 
But on the way we discovered some more important points. Turkey plays a very noteworthy role in the trade of the plants in the region.

What is the role of Turkey in the plant business of the region?
Turkey’s ornamental plants export and import figures are both rising steadily within the last 10 year period. As cut flower is still Turkey’s most important export product, in recent years export figures of other live plants are also rising rapidly. Turkey is also an importing country for many ornamental plants. Import quantities of the country are on the rise. 
Especially on the live plants field we serve as an interesting bridge. The big Turkish Construction contractors are building various projects in Middle East, North Africa and Central Asian Turkish Republics.  At the end of these projects the landscaping business is usually given to a Turkish landscaping contractor. These landscaping contractors are trying to supply the demand firstly from the internal market and then by imports mainly from the European countries and mainly from Italy. Turkish customers are among the most important purchasers of the Italian plant companies. 
On the other hand, in recent years the municipalities have been investing in parks and garden landscaping, and private construction companies are making spectacular landscaping agreements in the modern housing complexes they build in big cities. It is observed that the use of ornamental plants in these landscaping projects creates liveliness in the industry. 
All these main facts explain how Turkey is continuously growing its imports and exports mainly in the live plants industry.

From the picture you are describing, we understand that the aim of the exhibition is bigger than the Antalya Expo 2016 target. What can you say?
We are starting Florplant Exhibition in Antalya in order to facilitate for a better promotion of the Turkish ornamental plants and landscaping industries in national and international scale. We aim to form up an environment where importers, exporters, producers, suppliers, landscape designers and contractors can meet each other and develop their mutual business relations.
We are inviting professionals, managers, and executives from the hotels, gardens, municipalities’ parks, construction contractors, plant &amp; supplies exporters, importers, traders from our entire region to join us in this new and promising exhibition. 
We are eager to create an ornamental plants and landcaping exhibition where European producers can meet with Turkish, Middle East, North Affrica and Central Asia professionals in Turkey.

But why in Turkey and not in other Middle East country?
Another important advantage of Turkey is the non Shengen Visa Regime. Turkey is not in the Schengen Visa region. This makes it an easy accessible country for almost all Russian Speaking World, Middle East and North Africa countries citizens. Thus, many professional that have Visa difficulties and cannot visit European Exhibitions are eager to visit a similar international exhibition in Turkey.
Considering this political fact too, we can say that Florplant, in Antalya is a potential meeting place that the professionals from Turkey, Europe, Middle East and Central Asia can meet for fruitful business

But can Antalya host such an international event that you describe?
Yes surely it can! Maybe better than any other city in Turkey! Antalya is the capital of Tourism with 850 four and five star hotels that have a capacity of 550,000 beds. In 2010 Antalya hosted 10,000,000 of tourists. It has the second biggest international airport of Turkey it has plenty of direct flights from many north European cities and Russian Speaking countries. Moreover it is not a big city without traffic jam problems. This means that you can spend your evening times in one of the opportunities that the city life is offering you.

What is the profile of the exhibition? How big you plan it?
In the first years we are planning to host around 100 companies in a total area of net 3,500 sqm. Our aim is to attract at least 10 international exhibitors from 5 different countries.  We aim to attract a total of 3,000 profesional visitors. It is not a big start initially. But we can predict that the exhibition will grow year by year. 
What products are going to be exhibited? What is the profile of the professional visitors? 
Florplant has two main sectors. One is ornamental plants and the second is the landscaping. Thus you will see many live plant producers. Mainly outdoor and indoor plants. From the initial applications we see that there is also an interest from the football and golf field builders, greenkeepers, and suppliers. On the other hand, we expect to have exhibitors from different parts of the landscaping business. As for the professional visitors, we are expecting greenkeepers, park managers from the hotels industry and municipalities. We are also expecting landscape engineers, garden designers and construction companies landscape executives. Moreover we believe that we will see  many international traders from middle east and Arab World. 

What would you offer for Russian companies to be interested in Florplant, what do you think could be interesting for them? Why should Russian companies come to visit or even to exhibit?
We are planning Florplant to be an international trade meeting where national and foreign importers and exporters of the industry can show in the Turkish market.Of Courese there are very nice and important similar exhibition in Russia. But we offer the opportunity to Russian companies that would like to buy pot flowers, cut flowers, and live plants from Turkey to meet with more producers and more exporters that may not had the opportunity to show up in Russian Exhibitions. 
Moreover the city of Antalya offers a nice opportunities with its weather, hotels and entertainment. Thus Russian traders can combine holidays and business for few days.  

Beyond the exhibitors what is the Social Program of the exhibition? Do you plan any parallel events to make the exhibition worth to visit?
Yes there are some interesting events that are going to take place during the Exhibition.
First of all I would like to mention that Turkish Ornamental Plants and Supplies Exporters Union with the support of the Turkish Ministry of Economics have organized a buying mission. There will be buyers invited from Turkmenistan, Kazakhstan, Iraq, Iran, Azerbaijan, UAE, Qatar, Russian Federation, Ukraine, Germany, UK. This is a program that aims to support the Turkish exporters to meet with important buyers from these countries.
Another very important event is organized by the Italian Chamber of Commerce in İzmir (CCII). The CCII is organizing Bilateral Meetings Program for the Italian companies that would like to use this opportunity, come to Turkey to find new Turkish and Middle East customers that are going to visit the exhibition. 
In order to facilitate these entire B2B bilateral meetings program we have prepared special software the will help the parties to request appointments from each other, before the exhibition to be held in the exhibition. The aim is to try to organize the agenda of each professional visitor and exhibitor in order to use the time as efficient as possible. The software is working online in our website www.florplant.org/en 
Moreover there will be a panel with the participation of the industry’s leading association presidents or executives of Turkey. The panel will be held in Turkish and English and there will be simultaneous translation. The aim of the panel will be to give a picture of the Turkish Ornamental Plant Industry to all interested foreign buyers or sellers that would like to enhance their trade with Turkey. 
All the detailed program of the exhibition will be published in the website of the exhibition.
What do you do to attract all this audience? How do you advertise?
We have visited 5 international exhibitons so far. We have distributed brochures to the interested exhibitor companies. The exhibitons in which we could find the opportunity to introduce Florplant are Iberflora 2010 in Valencia- Spain; Hortifair 2010 in Amsterdam, the capital city of Holland; IPM Essen 2011 in Essen-Germany, Hipotechnika 2011 in Atina the capital city of Greece, Salon Du Vegetal 2011 in Angers-France and lastly Euroflora 2011 in Genova,Italy.
We have conducted advertising campaigns with 10 Turkish industry magazines and 12 international magazines . The ad pages of Florplant exhibition that are put down by native languages of each country will be published on various magazines in different months between April and September during 2011. More specifically, these magazines belong to  Bahrein, Egypt, Jordan, Iran, Israel, Italy,  Netherland,  Russia, Spain,  Greece and Taiwan. We will share all the ad pages of Florplant  published in these magazines at our websites as soon as we get them. 
To maintain our advertising via Internet , our banners will be on publication in 9 domestic portals and 10 portals abroad till the date of our exhibition. The industry's leading landscape, agriculture and plant portals are included among them. 
We have established an exhibition website at www.florplant.com from where you can obtain all the detailed information about Florplant and follow up each step we take. Our website is active in both English and Turkish. Moreover we send out a Turkish newsletter to 3.950 people in Turkey every 2 weeks with the aim of presenting our exhibition to the domestic market and we also transmit an English newsletter to 9.250 people abroad monthly. We are online in Facebook and Twitter in Turkish-English so as to be in touch with those who want to follow us on social media. www.facebook.com/florplant and www.twitter.com/florplant for Florplant Ornamental Plants and Landscaping Exhibition. Just Click!
Is there anything else that you would like to add?
We are aware that each important Exhibition has its own trade potential. We are trying to create a new potential. We are inviting the all the companies from Europe, Mediterranean Region, Middle East, Middle Asia that are interested to sell to Turkey or to buy from Turkey to join us whether as exhibitors or as visitors. But I would like to remind once more to not expect a big exhibition. Florplant is organized for the first time this year.  But we are sure that it will open new horizons and it will become an important a new meeting platform for the industry professionals.
- - -
OPINIONS
- - -
Teoman Akçalı
There is no doubt that Florplant Ornamental Plants and Landscaping Exhibition, which will have a direct impact on our city’s social and economic structure and increase information flow among the industry components, is going to make a great contribution to our industry in local, regional, national and international sense. 
We thank Agoras Exhibition Services on behalf of all our colleagues and industry members due to its brave initiative that will break a new ground in our city. We will be happy to be together with our colleagues and industry members in this exhibition which is self-focused on developing itself and the city. We are supporting the exhibition that we believe will be beneficial for all institutions, associations and people who aim a fruitful business.
Teoman Akçalı 
TMMOB The Chamber of Landscape Architects 
Board Chairman of Antalya Branch  
- - -
Osman Bağdatlıoğlu 
We follow and appreciate Florplant Ornamental Plants and Landscape Exhibition initiated by Agoras Exhibitions in order to contribute preparations of Antalya Project, Expo 2016. 
Agoras Exhibitions, the slogan of which is "Investment in the World's Green”, aims to organize an international exhibiton which will keep on after Expo 2016 and contribute to the growth of Turkish Ornamental Plants Industry through exportation. As Ornamental Plants Promotion Group, we also support this exhibition related to the vision of raising up our country's ornamental plants exports to 1 billion €. 
We will be glad to see neighbor countries' industry professionals who request to trade with ornamental plants manufacturers and exporters of Turkey, in Florplant Ornamental Plants and Landscape Exhibition which will be held on 28 September - 1 October, in Antalya Glass Pyramid.
President of Ornamental Plants Promotion Group
Osman Bağdatlıoğlu
- - - 
This year, Agoras Exhibition Services is organizing an exhibition on ornamental plants used in landscape architecture and applications which we have felt the lack of it for a long time. We, as regional producers, are supporting the only exhibition of our region that will get outdoor, indoor ornamental plans producer and the other industry representatives together.
We especially think that Botanic Expo 2016, which will be held in Antalya in 2016, will create a significant business volume and bring a nice vivacity in ornamental plants and landscape architecture industries.  As producer and implementer companies, we faithfully believe that Florplant Ornamental Plants and Landscaping Exhibition is going to provide a good oppurtunity to the industry in the preparation process of Expo 2016. 
We appreciate the national and international promotional activities of Agoras and we also expect to see foreign visitors, hotel managers, municipal parks and gardens managers, landscape architects of construction companies, landscape architecture offices and everyone interested in the industry in Florplant Exhibition, 2011.
We invite all ornamental plants producers and our colleagues to the exhibition.
Tarık Dede
President of Mediterannean Ornamental Plants Producers Association]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201108/29/10-13-31-56-14.gif]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[Plant|Turkey|Green]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Industry News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[AGORAS Fuarcılık Hizmetleri Ltd. Şti.]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-08-29 10:13</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[2011 Chelsea Flower Show]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=224]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[By/ Taiwan Orchid Growers AssociationCompleted Taiwan Image Landscape Display photoThe 2011 Chelsea Flower Show was held from May 24 to 28 this year at the Royal Chelsea Hospital in London, England. T]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp;Completed Taiwan Image Landscape Display photo
By/ Taiwan Orchid Growers Association

&nbsp;

The 2011 Chelsea Flower Show was held from May 24 to 28 this year at the Royal Chelsea Hospital in London, England. The Chelsea Flower Show is the largest flower and garden show held in England. It is not only the most time-honored show with the greatest level of public participation, it is a big celebration in English life. The organizer, the Royal Horticultural Society (RHS), is a non-profit charity organization that joins together gardening industries and consumers to promote gardening knowledge and education. The exhibit area covered 45,000 sq. meters &nbsp;this year. A total of 16 nations (includes Taiwan, Japan, France, Germany, Australia, South Africa, Thailand, Barbados, Holland, Iceland, Zimbabwe, Morocco and New Zealand) joined the show. Over 650 outstanding businesses and groups participated in the show and 170,000 people attended the show over the five day period.&nbsp;
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; The attention given to Chelsea Flower Show reflects the strong influence of gardening on British society. About a month before the show opens, the news media starts to report on the show&rsquo;s progress. The BBC broadcasts programming at fixed times each day to give in-depth reports on topics ranging from site introductions and show participants. The show is divided into indoor and outdoor exhibition spaces: the indoor exhibition area showcases garden plants, flower and flower arrangement displays and indoor cut flower decorations and the outdoor exhibition area features garden design &amp; landscaping and sales of related consumer gardening products. Fresh flowers are not sold at the general site. Advance orders are taken and then delivered to your doorstep. The show participants put their most exceptional flowers on display and keep them in their best selling condition throughout the show and take advance orders from the general public and other show participants.&nbsp;
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; This year was the second time the Association has participated in the Chelsea Flower Show. The theme of this year&rsquo;s landscape design was Wedding of the Century &ndash; The Fragrance of Joy. The piece was a 91 square meter landscape design that showcased the beauty of Taiwan orchids. The primary floral material used in the landscape was Taiwan&rsquo;s most representative flower, the Phalaenopsis orchid. The lead roles in the design were shared by the no. 1 export large blossom &ldquo;V3&rdquo; and the large pink blossom &ldquo;Phal. Ming-Hsing Eagle&rdquo;which were accompanied by numerous other colors and varieties of Phalaenopsis. By putting the broad diversity of Taiwan orchids on display, the landscape design vividly respresents Taiwan&rsquo;s Phalaenopsis kingdom. In addition to Phalaenopsis, Cattleya, Paphiopedilum and Oncidium also played major roles in the display. Using a minimal framework, hundreds of orchid varieties were skillfully arranged to convey the emotions of joy, love, passion and completeness and wish the Prince and Princess all the happiness in life.&nbsp;
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; The exceptional image of Taiwan orchid that was successfully presented at the Chelsea Flower Show attracted garden industry participants and flower aficionados from countries around the world and earned a gold medal, the highest honor awarded by the judges.
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; At the May 23 preview, the association invited two models to don wedding gowns to add a spirit of wedding bliss to the Taiwan image landscape display. In the afternoon, Taiwan's Representative to the UK Katharine Chang and Director Donald Lu from the Taiwan Trade Centre in London visited the Taiwan image landscape display set up by the association. Also during the afternoon on the same day, Her Majesty Queen Elizabeth II came to observe the display. For this occasion, a new variety of Phalaenopsis orchid named Dtps. Elizabeth II was prepared in her honor. The Queen was pleasantly surprised when Rep. Katharine Chang presented it to her. Later on, the finalist in the Plant of the Year Award category, a Phal. Ming-Hsing Eagle Phalaenopsis orchid with 20 large pink blossoms, was presented to the Queen. Prince Charles and Camilla, the Duchess of Cornwall, also attended the Taiwan exhibition area for the first time. Camilla praised the use of the elegant and distinguished charm of Taiwan orchids to create a dignified and graceful royal wedding atmosphere. The Association presented Chiada Ella, cultivated by National Chiayi University to the Duchess of Cornwall. Rep. Katharine Chang accompanied the Queen to the presentation given by Prince Albert II of Morocco on the Status of Taiwan&rsquo;s Orchid Industry where he commended the diversity and richness of Taiwan&rsquo;s orchid varieties. &nbsp;&nbsp;
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; The Association put on display an extensive variety of orchids at the Taiwan image landscape display. In addition to receiving a visit from the Queen of England, the display also attracted considerable amount of attention from the media and landscaping professionals. In order to promote their orchid brands, Taiwan not only needs to offer excellent quality but also has to find ways to promote and market their orchids through the media in order to enhance the promotional effect. Therefore, the Chelsea Flower Show is an important promotional site for Taiwan orchid marketing. From the exposure gained from the Queen&rsquo;s visit and media reports, Taiwan orchid brands entered a world stage and were gratefully accepted into the hearts of the English people.
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;
&nbsp;Rep. Katharine Chang presents a new variety of Phalaenopsis orchid Dtps. Elizabeth II to the Queen]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201108/24/09-04-52-68-15.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Flower Supplier News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-08-24 08:57</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Our goal is to deliver stable quality which is also our strong suit.]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=223]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Facing economic globalization and liberalization trends and following entry in the WTO, Taiwan's agricultural sector will be heavily impacted by market opening and free competition. Due to the growing]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp;Facing economic globalization and liberalization trends and following entry in the WTO, Taiwan's agricultural sector will be heavily impacted by market opening and free competition. Due to the growing economic liberalization, Taiwan must adjust their business and industry structure. In order to accommodate market demand, our company actively cultivates fine quality orchids to improve our technical service and raise competitiveness. The best equipment is put to use in order to reduce orchid viral cross-contamination, offer stable quality and achieve greater customization.
The chief advantages of Taiwan's orchid industry is its rich trove of species and strong breeding capabilities. These advantages can be clearly shows at orchid shows around the world With respect to Phalaenopsis orchids, this is especially true for V3 and amabilis. The mainstay V3 orchid at our company is a large white blossom variety. Our goal is to deliver stable quality which is also our strong suit.
At present, Japan is a chief export market. Buyers are always pleased with our orchid quality. The growth of the Phalaenopsis orchid industry from a small-scale domestic operation to a large-scale international industry has spurred the development of the tissue culture seedling industry. Now, other types of orchids such as Paphiopedilum orchids and Oncidium orchids are starting to make their presence known in world markets. Though we share in the joy of this progress, there are still some concerns out there. If Taiwanese companies do not continue to expand into overseas export markets, what direction can Taiwan's orchid industry take in the future? Faced with these future challenges and international competition, how many domestic orchid operations will be able to survive? Regardless of what may happen, there is one thing for certain &ldquo;those results gained from hard work and struggle will last the longest. &rdquo; In the following one or two years, the orchid industry will pass through a tough and arduous challenge. Quality will be a key factor in deciding whether Taiwan's orchids can remain a leading player internationally so guaranteeing exceptional quality is a major objective in our company's development.
&nbsp;]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201108/22/11-21-43-13-15.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Flower Supplier News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-08-22 11:21</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[High quality orchids produced and marketed with corporate management techniques]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=222]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Taida Horticultural Co., Ltd. was founded in 1981. We have been specializing in orchids breeding, tissue culture, mass cultivation, healthy plants control and worldwide export of all size, including f]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp;Taida Horticultural Co., Ltd. was founded in 1981. We have been specializing in orchids breeding, tissue culture, mass cultivation, healthy plants control and worldwide export of all size, including flask plants, young plants, medium, mature and flowering plants, of various kinds of orchids. Over the past decades, we have grown a tremendous volume of Phalaenopsis, Cattleya, Oncidium and other species. Thanks to the know-how acquired and the years of experience, we have become one of the most famous orchid growers in Taiwan with overseas branches located in N.J and N.Y, U.S.A. We firmly believe the future of orchid kingdom lies in the knowledge and experience of variety breeding and research.
Our goal is to meet all the needs of different customers from all over the world with high quality and the reasonable price. Standing by &ldquo;customer first&rdquo; philosophy, we constantly strive to provide the very best products to our customers to achieve complete satisfaction and create win-win situation.&nbsp;
&nbsp;Pen-chih, Lai who is our company&rsquo;s president and holds the position of chairman of Taida Horticultural as well does not only contribute to the Taiwan orchid by serving as the chairman of phalenopsis orchids committee in T.P.A but also as the president of International Commercial Orchid Grower Organization (ICOGO) which is a worldwide orchid grower organization with its headquarters being registered with CA, U.S.A and open to all enthusiastic parties in the orchid business.&nbsp;
Pen-chih hope, in the term to come, local symposiums will be held at the main growing regions to enhance the business knowledge and information exchange, application and authorization for variety right. We wish to encourage orchids&rsquo; consumption, beautify our daily life by means of our meager strength and moreover, to have the orchid trade blooming rapidly.
&nbsp;]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201108/19/17-55-14-35-15.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Garden Supplier News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-08-19 17:54</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Champion Orchid Nursery   Cultivating Beautiful, Charming and Elegant Orchids   We present Flask, Various Size of Plants & Flower Plants]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=221]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Taiwans Orchids are well-known in the orchids world. People all around the world naturally think of Taiwan when talking about orchids. And when they discuss colorful and abundant varieties of novelty ]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp;Taiwan&rsquo;s Orchids are well-known in the orchids world. People all around the world naturally think of Taiwan when talking about orchids. And when they discuss colorful and abundant varieties of novelty orchids, Champion Orchid Nursery is always with a very high reputation.&nbsp;
Champion Orchid Nursery has been presenting the very beautiful Phalaenopsis, Oncidium, Cattleya in terms of flask, small, medium, big plants and flowering plants with an excellent performance over 15 years. Their team is specialized in cultivation, production and marketing. The nursery has been presenting various varieties and different sizes of plants. As they have already supported their customers to develop the orchids business successfully, for example Asia, America, Europe, Oceania &amp; South Africa and so on.&nbsp;
In order to maintain the best quality, healthy and stable production plants of the beautiful orchids to the international market, Champion Orchid Nursery has their own nurseries and laboratory totally 30,000M2 located in Taiwan and China with 80 employees. It is a systematic attempt to strengthen them providing the abundant varieties with the best quality plants. Champion Orchid Nursery has also cooperates with a number of growers in Taiwan as a team, and to supply their customers with more varieties to reach annual capacity of three million plants.
Basically Taiwan orchids industry was originally organize by the people who cultivate orchids with pleasures. The President of Champion Orchid Nursery, Lu Tse - Ming was also a small orchids grower twenty years ago. He has been devoted his effort to transform his farm operation into a full-fledged industrialize orchid business wisely. Moreover, he was the first Chairman of the Taiwan Orchid Growers Association. During his term that he has been organized four international orchids shows successfully in Taiwan since 2000. Last year it was a well received of Asia-Pacific Orchid Conference that was also personally organized by him. During our talk, it was obviously to see his hard work characters and contribution in promoting the orchid industry in Taiwan. It definitely shows us the capability of Champion Orchid Nursery.]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201108/18/10-33-30-19-34.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Flower Supplier News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-08-18 10:31</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[The Domestic Leader in Flower Supplies? Beauty Cloud Xingyes Steps Out Globally from their Strong Position in Taiwan]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=220]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Beauty Cloud Xingyes is crossing into its 15th year of business. Prior to establishing their own brand, the company was an OEM manufacturer that focused on injection molded toys and hair ornaments. As]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[ Beauty Cloud Xingyes is crossing into its 15th year of business. Prior to establishing their own brand, the company was an OEM manufacturer that focused on injection molded toys and hair ornaments. As a result of the impact of the rising OEM market in China, Beauty Cloud Xingyes decided to create their own brand and specialize in the development and manufacture of flower supplies. The flower and orchard fields just began to take off in the 1990’s. After successfully establishing itself as an industry supplier, the company has steadily grown to become the largest flower supply manufacturer in Taiwan.
Starting from the successful development of Taiwan’s first plant tray, Beauty Cloud Xingyes has always been strongly dedicated to product quality, meeting customer requirements and developing products that conform to trends and industry needs. By introducing new plastic molding machines, fully automated production and computerized, operator-free manufacturing processes, manpower costs have been reduced which allows the company to offer the best quality products at the most economical prices. 
The current major products offered by Beauty Cloud Xingyes includes assorted sizes of plant trays, plant pot, environmentally friendly corn starch nursery pot and other various flower supplies. Plant trays and plant pots are their mainstay products. With regard to flower supplies, PVC coated wire and orchid & flower clips are their highlight products this year. Beauty Cloud Xingyes takes great pride in the reliability of their products. Due to the volume production and reasonable prices, the company has established a strong reputation and name in the industry. 
At present, about 60% of Beauty Cloud Xingyes products are exported to countries such as Holland, the United States, Canada and Japan. The domestic market comprises 40% of sales. In the future, the company will do more than just offer exceptional products at competitive prices. In order to serve a broader range of customers, their scope of business will be expanded to other overseas markets in the hope that high quality ‘Made in Taiwan’ products can play an irreplaceable role in international markets.]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201108/17/17-59-03-65-4302.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Flower Supplier News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-08-17 17:58</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Emerging from Asia, the Flora group cultivates high-quality orchids to explore European and other international flower market.]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=219]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Being the driving force of global horticulture business, the Taiwan Flora creates limitless innovative power!History:    In 1985, the Flora International Co., Ltd. was established, with main business ]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[ Being the driving force of global horticulture business, the Taiwan Flora creates limitless innovative power!
 
History: 
        In 1985, the Flora International Co., Ltd. was established, with main business of importing different kinds of flower bulbs, young plants and seeds from the whole world. It also introduced new varieties and cultivation technologies from overseas to growers in Taiwan.
        In 1994, in order to reduce cultivation costs, bring down growers’ risks and supply efficient young plants to growers, the Chin-Jing nursery, as part of the Flora International Co., Ltd. was set up. There flower cutting, breeding, propagation and transplantation work was done.
        In 1996, to apply the successful business model of Flora International Co., Ltd to mainland China, the China Flora group was established. The China Flora invested production nurseries in Kunming, Guangzhou and Inner Mongolia autonomous region, to supply fresh cut flowers and potted plants to each sale outlet in mainland China. Now cooperating with professional breeding nurseries and subcontracting nurseries, the China Flora is operating approximate 300 ha. 
        The Flora group has set up tissue culture labs in Taiwan and Kunming, China. The virus-free mother bottle was produced in Taiwan and supplied to China as well, providing economical flasks to young plant cultivation nurseries.
        In 2003, due to the increasing needs of pot plant orchids in European market, the Flora group quickly expanded its international orchid market shares, in cooperation with its overseas partners. The pot orchid nurseries in Taiwan, China, Thailand and Vietnam were built up.
        In 2005, in order to develop European market, the Flora group set up French and British nurseries, supplying various varieties of high-quality pot plant orchids to local wholesalers and chain supermarkets, like ASDA, Morrison.
Meanwhile, we started to develop van sales system to explore garden center and high-end florist shop business.
        In 2008, the Flora group expanded Flossan Sarl sale booth in Rungis to offer high-class, high price pot plant orchids to local wholesalers, including Paris leading florist shop Moulie.
        In 2009, the V-flora (UK) Ltd., the British nursery of Flora Group, produced over 1,000,000 pots. There are 3 packing lines and 1 arrangement line in V-flora (UK), providing orchids to chain supermarkets, Floraholland Auction and garden centers. V-Flora (UK) Ltd. sold 1,000,000 pot plants in 2009 and is on the increase.
        In 2010, Presenting the innovation of the industry, the newly founded Orchids Plantation Division in Tainan uses the Dutch construction, the explicit system to control the environment, the RFID to ensure the quality and quantity of the plants in every process. The new greenhouse occupied over 3.3 hectares will produce over 8 millions mini phalaenopsis per year.
 
]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201108/16/17-38-18-42-15.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Flower Supplier News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-08-16 17:37</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Miao Hua Orchids Sets Sights on Cut Flower Sales and Volume Production to Transform the Paphiopedilum Orchid Market]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=218]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Located in Taiwans Changhua county, Miao Hua Orchids have dedicated itself to Paphiopedilum orchid farm operation and seedling cultivation for over a decade since its establishment in 2000. Focused on]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[ Located in Taiwan’s Changhua county, Miao Hua Orchids have dedicated itself to Paphiopedilum orchid farm operation and seedling cultivation for over a decade since its establishment in 2000. Focused on long-term cultivation of rare Paphiopedilum orchid varieties, the company offers many exceptional and distinctive varieties to attract buyers. A broad range of orchids are produced in small batches and exported in flask seedling, large seedling (close to flowering plant), bud and flowering plant form to Japan, US, Europe, China and Southeast Asia.  
        The Paphiopedilum orchid is also called the lady slipper orchid due to the shape of their labellum. Besides having a unique flower shape, Paphiopedilum orchids have blossoms that range from large to small size, remarkable colors and spot patterns. Beyond the hundreds of native species of this plant, the number of Paphiopedilum orchid varieties when hybrids of native species are included amount to more than one thousand. Being very diverse in scope and extending over a broad range, Paphiopedilum orchids are very special in comparison to other types of orchids. They also have flowering periods of over one month which makes them very appealing to orchid enthusiasts from abroad. As the farm grew from hobbyist niche to a trading scale grower, suitable Maudiae type strains of Paphiopedilum orchids were chosen as commercial varieties to satisfy market requirements.  
        Paphiopedilum orchids are known to be a kind of orchid that have seeds which are hard to germinate. As a result, these orchids were originally limited to niche markets. Recently the situation has changed. Paphiopedilum orchids are starting to attract wide market attention and demand is steadily increasing. The only problem is the limited number of seedling sources. In order to respond to end user demand in the ornamental flower market, it is necessary to increase the supply and cultivation area for Paphiopedilum orchids. Miao Hua Orchids has introduced fine quality native species of Paphiopedilum orchids for selection and breeding. In addition to selecting excellent quality varieties that are suitable for Taiwan cultivation, Miao Hua Orchids have stable quality and exceptional breeding technology. This enables them to cultivate distinctive orchid varieties under superior conditions that overcome the obstacles that appear in the large scale growing of seedlings. Those who cooperate with Miao Hua Orchids possess the absolute competitive advantage gained from quick market entry. 
        Besides supplying orchids to the hobbyist market, Miao Hua Orchids has also set its sights on cut flower market and plans to sell potted flowers. By producing large quantities of seedlings to supply dedicated traders with Paphiopedilum orchids, Miao Hua Orchids has become the most representative volume cultivator for domestic and foreign markets. Possessing a comprehensive range of native species, the farm holds a major competitive advantage with respect to varieties and volume production which gives them room to grow and the power to breakthrough bottlenecks in selection and breeding quantities. Miao Hua Orchids plans to develop their business towards cut flower sales so that even more people can gaze upon the beautiful blossoms of Paphiopedilum orchids.
 ]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201108/15/17-06-21-11-15.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Flower Supplier News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-08-15 17:05</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Kingdom of Varieties Pursue Win-Win Situation]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=217]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Gan Lin Agriculture Co., Ltd, a large scale orchid grower in Taiwan, completed their latest phase of their greenhouse expansion this year. Possessing an 18,000 sq. meter production facility in Pingtun]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[ Gan Lin Agriculture Co., Ltd, a large scale orchid grower in Taiwan, completed their latest phase of their greenhouse expansion this year. Possessing an 18,000 sq. meter production facility in Pingtung County and greenhouses in the United States and Canada, Gan Lin Agriculture has a total production area that occupies 25,500 sq. meters and further expansion plans are in the works.  In operation for over three decades and having a presence in overseas markets for over 20 years, Gan Lin Agriculture is a leading Phalaenopsis orchid exporter.
        To respond to global environmental protection, energy conservation and carbon reduction trends, Gan Lin Agriculture spared no expense to invest in a heat pump system that uses heat exchange principles as a replacement for heavy oil heating in order to reduce carbon emissions. The replacement project is scheduled to be completed this year. The owner Kuo Chen-Hsiung pointed out that environmental protection has been a focus for Gan Lin Agriculture this year. The green, energy saving heat pump system is able to replace high polluting equipment while achieving the desired greenhouse heating and cooling effect. 
        Gan Lin Agriculture has accumulated much experience in breeding, production and marketing and established a stable pool of customers. Their overseas markets include North America, Europe and Japan. Kuo Chen-Hsiung stated overall sales increased by over 60% in 2009. In fact, the Canadian and U.S. markets which were at the epicenter of financial crisis grew by a remarkable 80% this year. Sales did decline slightly in European market in the first half of the year but improved significantly by the end of the year. With an annual production capacity of about three million plants, Gan Lin Agriculture is looking to expand future production to over five million plants per year. 
        The sales success of a company depends on their partnership with customers, as well as the attitude toward customer service.
        Gan Lin Agriculture Co., Ltd. has strived for establishing long-term relationship with business associates, by providing tailor-made services and supplies respectively.  
        Besides, we pursue mutual benefits!
        This year we have 175 varieties to meet wide ranges of customer needs and keep refined for win-win situation.
        Committed to operating a sustainable business, Kuo Chen-Hsiung is planning a stage-by-stage expansion of their greenhouse area in Taiwan, Canada and the United States in order to offer consistent product quality and maintain a stable product supply to provide the best service to customers. 
        Chairman Kuo Chen-Hsiung of Gan Lin Agriculture Co., Ltd has focused his efforts on new variety development and obtaining domestic and foreign patent rights to new plant varieties. For example, patents have been submitted and received for these ten product numbers in order to prevent reproduction and copying by others. Anyone who engages in this type of behavior will be subject to legal action. 
 ]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201108/12/16-58-27-18-15.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Flower Supplier News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-08-12 16:56</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Rays of Light Appear From the Dark? Flower Export Value Grows by 18.63%]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=216]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[According to statistics compiled by the Taiwans Council on Agriculture, total foreign exports of Taiwan flowers for the first 6 months of 2011 amounted to 23,065.16 metric tons. Total export value was]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[ According to statistics compiled by the Taiwan’s Council on Agriculture, total foreign exports of Taiwan flowers for the first 6 months of 2011 amounted to 23,065.16 metric tons. Total export value was US$85,167,900. Compared to the previous year, overall export volume increased by 12.43% and export value rose by 18.63%. 
The flowers and related seedlings exported by Taiwan can be divided into the cut flower, foliage, sod, flower bulb, flower seed, and live flowering plant categories. During this year, significant increases were seen in almost every category. Only rose and carnation in the cut flower,  Oncidium orchids in the flower seedlings and anthurium in the live flowering plant category had declined by 50% or more. These four items fell 85.71%, 68.29%, 75.47% and 66.67% respectively. 
With regard to the cut flower market, overall export volume increased by 2.19%. The top cut flower export by value and production value was Oncidium orchids. The total export volume for Oncidium orchids was 659.71 metric tons which represented a 7.57% increase compared to the previous year. Chrysanthemums ranked second with an export volume of 493.04 metric tons and an export amount of US$1,906,100. The export amount grew by 8.36% over the previous year. As for the growth rate, the category with the highest growth rate was “tulip, cut flowers”. Its export growth is 36.84%. The second fastest growing category was eustoma which had a growth rate of 36.17%. 
With regard to the flower seedlings or live flowering plant markets, export volumes display an overall upward trend. Phalaenopsis orchids were the best performing item. The export volume of this category of flower seedlings amounted to 563.3 metric tons, decreasing by 18.19% over the previous year. The export value was US$7,245,900, 8.38% than the year before. The export volume for live flowering plants totaled 3,506.32 metric tons, which represented a 17.99% increase over the previous year. The export value reached US$36,446,200 which was 22.24% higher than the previous year.
Looking back over the first half of 2011, flower markets, in general, experienced significant growth. Declines were also relatively minor and only a few items saw major declines. This shows that prospects are good for the flower market for the second half of this year. After navigating safely through the global financial storm, Taiwan’s flower market has been able to swiftly regain its footing in adverse conditions. The fighting spirit learned by Taiwanese people over the years is still strong. Though shafts of light have broken through the stormy clouds, Taiwan’s flower industry cannot let down its guard. It should respond to current trends to strengthen cooperation and interchanges with others in the domestic industry to build strength. Only by focusing on overseas markets and steadily unveiling fresh and innovative products can Taiwanese companies shine brightly in the market.
]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201108/11/08-49-20-92-15.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Flower Supplier News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-08-11 08:48</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Fitness from Superweigh]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=215]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Adedicated manufacturer of fitness products for health, wellness, home rehabilitation and active aging since 1986. Ideal for commercial, light commercial  home use. Product line includes treadmills, e]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp;Adedicated manufacturer of fitness products for health, wellness, home rehabilitation and active aging since 1986.
&bull;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Ideal for commercial, light commercial &amp; home use. Product line includes treadmills, elliptical, exercise bikes ,upright, recumbent, stepper and rowers.
&bull;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Holds over 100 patents , the ergonomics, multi-functionality, unique design ,construction, appearance of their fitness products have created a sensation throughout the industry.
&bull;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; EN957 class SA , CE , GS certified and has been awarded to a number of models and most raw materials are RoHS compliance.&nbsp; 
&bull;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; ISO 9001 approved. Made in Taiwan. Fully integrated process incorporating R&amp;D, testing , production, calibration, inspection &amp; shipment. Manufacturing performed exclusively at SEG facilities from steel tube process and robotic welding to painting and packaging. 
&bull;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Customer-friendly products known for good quality, competitive price, delivery &amp; after-sales service .
&bull;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Eco-friendly, steady introduction of exceptional products to bring healthy and balanced life.]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201107/27/17-07-24-39-15.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Sports Supplier News ]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-07-27 17:06</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Graduated Compression Concepts Usher in a New Age of Professional Athletic Compression Socks]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=214]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ I-M Sanitary Materials is primarily engaged in the RD and manufacture of medical rehabilitation products and sports protectors and combined the advantages in medical rehabilitation and sports injury ]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[   I-M Sanitary Materials is primarily engaged in the R&D and manufacture of medical rehabilitation products and sports protectors and combined the advantages in medical rehabilitation and sports injury fields in the industry and high quality service. In 2011, I-Ming Sanitary Materials formally unveiled their athletic compression socks which introduced medical, environmental protection and features of graduated compression concepts(20-30mmHg on ankle) to the athletic sock field and created an all-around athletic sock that offers true protection.
        The unique design of I-Ming athletic compression socks makes use of the scientific principles of graduated compression to offer graduated reduction of pressure from the ankle to the thigh. Specialized athletic socks have been designed for different sports and exercise to improve blood circulation. The company put its ergonomic expertise to work when designing the inner layer of the athletic socks. Left and right leg labels can be seen when the neck of the sock is folded open. The inner sections are specially designed to have their own individual functions so the sock can fully achieve its support, protection and cushioning effects. A nano silver fiber material is used in the ankle and heel sections for anti-bacteria and anti-odor effects. The bottom of the sole is breathable and well-ventilated. A cotton yarn material is used and the soles are thick woven. The special fibers have a soft, comfortable texture and possess excellent vibration absorption characteristics. Slightly thick athletic socks give firmness and agility to your stride during exercise. 
        Each pair of professional athletic socks is created through detailed planning and evaluation by their skilled and talented staff. Their socks are manufactured through the use of computerized design and advanced German machinery. The company has introduced three different knee socks for extreme speed, instant movement and long-lasting effect based on the characteristics and features of individual sports. Each section of the leg from the toe bones to knee joint is amply protected. The requirements of different levels of users from professional athlete to amateur are specifically defined (left and right leg) and many colors and styles offer custom variety so the users can choose the right sock based on their regular exercise habits and requirements.
        Their line of knee pad products not only has streamlined styling and four-sided elasticity but also provides more extensive protection to cruciate ligaments so long periods of knee exercise from sports like basketball and horse riding will not result in injury.
        I-M  professional pressure athletic socks and knee pads offer the best protection to fully prepare you for athletic activities. By reducing your chance of sports injury and increasing endurance, you can bring your best athletic form to your workouts and sporting events and develop your full potential and ability so you can achieve top performance.]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201107/22/17-12-12-42-477.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Sports Supplier News ]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-07-22 17:08</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Superior Industry Resource Utilization Easy to Operate Products Alexandave Industries Makes Use of Total Dedicated Service to Reach a New Milestone in the Fitness Equipment Industry]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=213]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[     Founded in 1980, Alexandave Industries Co., Ltd. started out as a trading company. At the end of the 1990s, the company successfully crossed over into the sporting goods development and manufactu]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;Founded in 1980, Alexandave Industries Co., Ltd. started out as a trading company. At the end of the 1990&rsquo;s, the company successfully crossed over into the sporting goods&rsquo; development and manufacturing field with a focus on weight training and fitness equipment R&amp;D and production. In order to reduce business operation risk, the products were extended to steel and stone material product fields that the company was familiar with such as marble mosaic tables, gate fences and fireplaces over the past two years. In response to ageing society trends, Alexandave Industries has developed fitness and rehabilitation products with senior citizens in mind. By operating their business in a diverse but integrated manner, the company can provide customers with a broad assortment of products. Efforts have also been made in recent years to expand their product lines. This expansion has resulted in a steady increase in orders and shows that their efforts to diversify their operations are bearing fruit. Alexandave Industries products truly stand out with respect to function and appearance. As for more basic introductory level sporting goods, the company is able to provide OEM services that offer exceptional quality at competitive prices.&nbsp;
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; This year, Alexandave Industries mainstay products are plates and dumbbells made of high-end TPU material. This material is impact resistant and highly practical because it will not degrade over long periods of use. This year, an all-new three-hole design was incorporated into the plates which makes them easier to grip in order to offer greater convenience to users. Because TPU is an eco-friendly material, it can be recycled which reduces resource consumption. Alexandave Industries has also made refinements to their manufacturing processes that have shortened plastic injection molding times, increased production efficiency and raise production capacity. In addition to this, rigorous quality controls have been adopted to minimize defect rates and maximize customer satisfaction.&nbsp; 
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; With regard to business strategy, Alexandave Industries embraces their core values of kindness, integrity, equilibrium, simplicity &amp; innovation and integration for market operation. Skilled at utilizing industry resources and employing its own extensive R&amp;D experience, the company is able to offer exceptional products and services to customers. As for customer service, the goal of Alexandave Industries is to provide total solutions. It is not just about creating competitive products at a certain price. The products have to be able to meet those requirements that are not related to price competitiveness. As a result, the company has grown at an annual rate of 15%-20% since its establishment. 
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Alexandave Industries products are mainly mid high to high end quality level, and their export markets are located in Europe, Japan, Russia, and Canada. Proud of workmanship, functionality and attractive appearance of their products, the company wants to focus on expanding its overseas business in the future and directly control development in the U.S. market to raise product recognition and market share. In addition, Alexandave Industries will continue to refine their products and services, expand production capacity for TPU material products, raise product competitiveness to do their part for their environment and display their commitment to offering the best quality products to customers and users.]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201107/19/17-46-29-19-15.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Sports Supplier News ]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-07-19 17:42</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Tonic Fitness Technology Crosses New Milestones in Health Management]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=212]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Founded by President Andy Wu in 1985, Tonic Fitness Technology, by adhering to their business mission of innovative technology and quality first, specializes the development, production and sales of e]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[ Founded by President Andy Wu in 1985, Tonic Fitness Technology, by adhering to their business mission of “innovative technology and quality first”, specializes the development, production and sales of exercise and fitness equipment. Firmly believing that R&D is the foundation of company growth, Tonic Fitness Technology has crossed many technological milestones over the years. Being a leader in the industry, the company has won many new product awards and all of their products have received CE, UL and ETL certification.  
        In order to respond to constantly changing market trends and consumer demands, Tonic Fitness Technology has always focused on developing products that conform to the needs of people. By combining the strengths of industry, academia and R&D institutions, the functions and specifications from different fields can be integrated into products. Tonic Wellness R & D Center was founded to establish exercise physiology systems and promote the development of exercise and fitness trends in order to elevate fitness equipment into a platform that offers a range of exercise, medical and health services. 
 

        Tonic Fitness Technology has entered long-term R&D and production agreements with many famous global fitness equipment manufacturers. In order to prevent over reliance on certain markets and increase the added value of their products, Tonic Fitness Technology has steadily developed products with special functions to spread into different markets, diversify their investment risks and meet the needs of different consumer groups. By keeping their focus on localization and innovation management, the company can develop products that stand out with respect to design and functionality. In addition, Tonic Fitness Technology incorporates mind and body management concepts into their product functions. Through body and mind balance and coordination, people can learn health knowledge and management, improve their life functions, improve interpersonal relations and live longer, vigorous lives.
          Faced with the American economic downturn in 2008, skyrocketing material costs and the appreciation of the New Taiwan Dollar, the entire team at Tonic Fitness Technology draws upon their vision, enthusiasm and drive to develop innovative niche products that raise company profitability and open up new blue ocean in the field of health management.]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Sports Supplier News ]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-07-18 11:25</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Tung Yi Steel Wire is a 42-Year Old Pioneer in Taiwan’s Steel Cable Business]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=211]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Tung Yi Steel Wire's President Vincent Huang originally worked for the renowned China First Steel Ropes Mfg. Lat from 1958 to 1968. Working his way up the corporate ladder from technician to plant man]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp;Tung Yi Steel Wire's President Vincent Huang originally worked for the renowned China First Steel Ropes Mfg. Lat from 1958 to 1968. Working his way up the corporate ladder from technician to plant manager, he gained much expertise in the fields of production technology, product R&amp;D and quality management. Due to the specialization level in the steel cable business, Vincent Huang firmly believes in serving his customers well, being sincere and trustworthy in business and focusing on innovation and top quality. In 1969, Vincent Huang founded Tung Yi Steel Wire that has been in business for over forty years now which makes the company one of the pioneers of Taiwan's steel cable business.&nbsp;   
&nbsp;

&nbsp;The company has always dedicated itself to the field of steel cable technology. Starting out in the bicycle field, Tung Yi Steel Wire has recently expanded its business to the exercise equipment field. Manufacturing surfing, mountain climbing, exercise and skiing equipment famous in Japan, the company's president Vincent Huang has participated in a wide range of international shows in order to look for fresh concepts from other companies to develop healthy products that conform to market requirements and possess unique characteristics for buyers from around the world. 
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Dedicated to product quality, Tung Yi Steel Wire has not only obtained European CE and Japan JIS certification but also applied for 70 plus patents in America, Japan, Germany and Taiwan. With regard to product development, the company works with academic bodies and the Industrial Technology Research Institute to research and manufacture steel cables for use with PVC, PU, nylon and other coating materials which offer excellent water and weather resistance properties. Exports currently comprise about 80% of sales. Tung Yi Steel Wire products can be found in Germany, America, Japan, South America and Russia. In the future, the company will strive to develop even better products for its customers and upgrade its brand image so their products can penetrate further into global markets and company business can vault to new heights.]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Sports Supplier News ]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-07-15 16:57</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Steelflex -  An experience of Health, Enjoyment, Value, and Eco-Friendly]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=210]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[When Joong Chenn Industry unveiled the Steelflex Maga Power series of weight training machine in 2010, there was a wave of positive response from fitness and exercise markets in the U.S., Europe and o]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp;When Joong Chenn Industry unveiled the Steelflex Maga Power series of weight training machine in 2010, there was a wave of positive response from fitness and exercise markets in the U.S., Europe and other regions around the globe. Later in 2011, Joong Chenn Industry launched a brand new M3D multi-function weight training machine to satisfy market requirements.   
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; There are a total of 4 models (M3DHL, M3DFC, M3DBR, M3DSM) of M3D weight training machine. Each machine model is equipped with multi-function training functions and even greater workout benefits can be obtained when combined with the trainer series. 
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; President Kelvin Wu expressed great confidence in the M3D series R&amp;D and market response. He added, most regular cable trainers are single muscle or single function products. Each model in the Steelflex M3D series has a multi-function training structure. For example, in addition to providing a stable movement range for the Smith machine, the M3DSM also has a front / rear movement range function that can overcome joint movement range limitations and reduce workout injuries. It also allows the trainer to offer greater benefits during training.
&nbsp;
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; In European, U.S. and other international exercise and fitness markets, a major market trend is exercise equipment with multiple exercise modes, explained Chairman James Chen. For product marketing, planning and R&amp;D of Steelflex, the goal was always to offer superior quality workmanship and a product that was highly competitive on the market. M3D series products have the greatest functionality and have become the representative machine on the market. For Steelflex, an all-out effort was made at innovation, R&amp;D and manufacturing levels to create an exercise equipment mode that conforms to human factor (ergonomic) requirements which delivering optimal workout benefits.&nbsp;&nbsp; 
 &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Steelflex&rsquo;s M3D series fitness equipment is one of a few top quality exercise machines that has come on the market in recent years that combines high safety, enjoyment (variety), value (quality / appearance) and is environmentally friendly. It is definitely worth trying out in person.&nbsp;]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201107/11/15-52-24-34-15.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Sports Supplier News ]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-07-11 15:48</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Chern Shianq Enterprise Continues to Make Great Strides Forward by Embracing the A-Plums Spirit]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=209]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[The business philosophy of Chern Shianq Enterprise over the past 20 years is to embrace and promote a spirit of pride towards A-Plums and focus on RD and innovation to provide a sustainable path of de]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp;The business philosophy of Chern Shianq Enterprise over the past 20 years is to embrace and promote a spirit of pride towards A-Plums and focus on R&amp;D and innovation to provide a sustainable path of development for the company.   
&nbsp;Chern Shianq Enterprise started off as specialized manufacturer of foam rubber parts and accessories for exercise and fitness equipment. Due to fast growth in business to export markets, the company&rsquo;s manufacturing facilities were moved to a plant in the Guan Tian Industrial Park in 1998. In 2002, the company received ISO9001 quality certification and formally launched their own A-Plums brand and expanded their original manufacturing facilities at Tainan&rsquo;s Guan Tian Industrial Park in 2009.&nbsp; 
&nbsp;

&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The creativity and quality of Chern Shianq products can be seen in their sports water bottle design. The curving bottle shape represents a clear break away from standard sport water bottle designs. A new bullet shaped bottle was launched in 2011 to offer a product that conforms to the rounded and streamlined style loved by Europeans. Safety and practical use requirements are met during manufacturing by using non-toxic materials suitable for use in products for human consumption. Products have also passed EU and US safety certification. Advantages like their free sliding and easy-cleaning bottle are the reasons why Chern Shianq products are the first choice of customers. 
  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &lsquo;A&rsquo; stands for top grade, number one products and &lsquo;Plums&rsquo; symbolizes the resilient and hardy qualities of the plum blossom. From the very beginning, Chern Shianq Enterprise has always been dedicated to providing excellent service quality and aesthetically styled and multi-functional products to the general public. As a result, Chern Shianq Enterprise products are highly valued in international markets which has led the company on a path to steady growth and progress.]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Sports Supplier News ]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-07-08 16:52</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Known for their Quality and Unique Design, Ying Uan Enterprise Products are Found Throughout the World]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=208]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Ying Uan Enterprise Co., Ltd, established in 1986, offers a wide variety of exercise equipment but specializes in the production of twist rope and other small-sized fitness equipment. Over the last tw]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp;Ying Uan Enterprise Co., Ltd, established in 1986, offers a wide variety of exercise equipment but specializes in the production of twist rope and other small-sized fitness equipment. Over the last twenty years, the company has gained a reputation for quality in international markets. A steady stream of products has been introduced to the marketplace which shows the strong development capabilities of the Taiwan sporting good industry.
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; In the early days, Ying Uan Enterprise specialized in the manufacture of twist ropes. Drawing upon their extensive experience with rubber materials, Chairman Hsu Yi-Kun and his material supplier jointly developed a special rubber material that could be widely used in twist ropes, luggage straps and motorcycles straps. The products that were made with the material developed by Chairman Hsu Yi-Kun were far safer and more durable than the products available at that time on the market. Later in 1998, Chairman Hsu Yi-Kun expanded his production line to include the manufacture of various kinds of small sized fitness equipment. A number of convenient and portable home-use fitness devices were designed that incorporated the unique twist rope manufactured by the company. 
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Lightweight, convenient and space saving are the key design features of Ying Uan Enterprise's small sized fitness equipment. The Master Gym is an easy-to-use and space saving fitness device. The user only has to fasten the clamp to the base or top of door panel. By holding the handle and footstrap, it can be extended in either direction based on your strength. It is great for home use or anywhere else you want to get a workout. Over the years, Chairman Hsu Yi-Kun has developed a series of smart and innovative products for the sporting goods market. The adjustable weight jump rope uses different weight cores that are fastened on the center of the jump rope to let the user increase or reduce the weight of the handles to suit one's own preference which provides users a better workout than regular jump ropes. Their exerciser wheel with twist rope combines an exerciser wheel and twist rope. The function of the twist rope is to use counterforce to allow the user to more easily complete the pull back motion. There is another twist rope that lets the user get a better full-body workout in a push-up stance from the push forward and pull back motion of the exercise wheel. 
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; In addition to unveiling a stream of smart and innovative products, Ying Uan Enterprise has invested a sizeable sum on a set of professional testing instruments to ensure better quality and design capabilities and the pull force, strength and durability attributes fully comply with international standards so the fitness equipment made by Ying Uan Enterprise. Therefore, consumers can be assured that their products are totally safe to use!

]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Sports Supplier News ]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-07-07 16:03</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Tzy Shenq Enterprise Wins Customer Trust through Exceptional Design and Commitment to Quality]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=207]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Founded in 1976, Tzy Shenq Enterprise Co., Ltd. started out as a plastic mold developer. In response to subsequent market changes, the company decided to shift their focus over to the product design a]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[Founded in 1976, Tzy Shenq Enterprise Co., Ltd. started out as a plastic mold developer. In response to subsequent market changes, the company decided to shift their focus over to the product design and manufacturing field. In operation for over 30 years, Tzy Shenq Enterprise has accumulated extensive experience in development, design and plastic injection molding &amp; assembly work. Drawing upon their all-in-one R&amp;D and production system and professional dedication to customer service, Tzy Shenq Enterprise has won broad customer recognition for its sports, recreational and agricultural tool products and successfully established a niche in export markets in Europe, U.S. and Japan which has made the company a leading developer and manufacturer of plastic injection molded products in Taiwan.&nbsp;
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Tzy Shenq Enterprise is skilled at incorporating market thinking into product development. Careful product positioning and market analysis has been effective in raising product competitiveness. Standardized work processes not only simplify manufacturing processes and reduce costs but also help to enhance product R&amp;D capability and production efficiency. In the field of industrial and academic cooperation, Tzy Shenq Enterprise has entered into development projects with academic institutions to expand its product range as well as offer a greater product selection and OEM services to customers. 
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; In addition to their professional R&amp;D capabilities, Tzy Shenq Enterprise has also invested large sums in manufacturing machinery and introduced precision instruments &amp; equipment. Through the use of CAE mold flow analysis, product design can be corrected in advance which reduces development risk and production costs as well as enabling the manufacture of precise and durable plastic injection molds. The company also has special processes for the injection molding of engineering plastic products. Through the use of material dehumidifying and drying equipment, mold temperature controllers and automated central supply systems, Tzy Shenq Enterprise can ensure that their injection molded products are high and stable quality.&nbsp; 
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Due to their strict product design requirements and rigorous attention paid to manufacturing equipment, Tzy Shenq Enterprise is able to accept business ranging for small plastic washers to engine covers for large construction machinery while providing customers with the very best service. In response to market challenges faced over the years, Tzy Shenq Enterprise has been awarded ISO 9001-2000, German TUV and Japanese JQA international certification so that the company can offer strict quality control and precise inspection and testing procedures to enable their products to pass a wide range of international inspection and quality standards.
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; In the future, Tzy Shenq Enterprise will continue on developing new products and provide total product design and OEM services to customers in a variety of fields. By standing by their business philosophy of innovation, excellence, customer focus and honest business practices, the company has earned the trust of customers and put the company on a path to sustainable development.



]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Sports Supplier News ]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-07-07 15:54</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Jiu Ling’s Innovative Chainless Recumbent Three-Wheel Bike Unlocks New Business Opportunities]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=206]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Established in 2008, Jiu Ling Co., Ltd. started out as a component, frame and paint OEM service provider. After having accumulated extensive experience and in-house mold making technology for over a d]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[Established in 2008, Jiu Ling Co., Ltd. started out as a component, frame and paint OEM service provider. After having accumulated extensive experience and in-house mold making technology for over a decade, the company decided to launch their own brand three years ago and develop a line of recumbent three-wheel bikes for recreational use. Jiu Ling chose to focus on one front wheel &ndash; two back wheel design. The advantages of a single front wheel design are shorter turning radius, better handling and greater agility. By equipping the bike with a large front wheel for faster speeds and smaller rear wheels to lower the center of gravity, the design is more stable and less likely to overturn. Its low frame design provides reduced wind resistance during pedaling and makes riding recumbent for long periods less fatiguing which provides greater safety and comfort.&nbsp;&nbsp; 
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Possessing many innovative designs and unique functions not available on other products, the main steering function is located at the back wheels to solve the steering difficulties experienced on three wheel bikes. This design makes it much easier to back up and even offers enjoyable bike drifting. The newly released model JIU-701 is foldable which makes it convenient to stow away. The bike also offers a one-of-a-kind chainless design which significantly reduces bike maintenance and effectively reduces the frame size. The eight-stage retractable mechanism with a 110 to 200 cm range can be adjusted to a level that optimally suits the height of rider so both children and adults can ride it safely.
&nbsp;

&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Originally developed for exercise and recreational needs, Jiu Ling&rsquo;s recumbent three-wheel bikes also come with complete post-sales service and quality guarantee. From the thank-you letters received from customers, Jiu Ling discovered that their bikes helped kids develop a sense of balance and aided the rehabilitation of people with physical disabilities which has inadvertently created new niche markets for their products.&nbsp; 

&nbsp;
 
&nbsp;

&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Jiu Ling insists on offering the highest quality products that are both innovative and practical. By combining a structure that emphasizes safety and high-class aerodynamic styling, the bike offers an ergonomic design and lifestyle-friendly accessories. R&amp;D, design, manufacturing and shipping is done exclusively in Taiwan. Test riding is done by dedicated personnel and the R&amp;D team then performs three sets on testing on products. Welding, calibration, hardness testing and long-term load testing has all passed U.S. certification. Jiu Ling has always shown a strong commitment to ensure that their products are extensively and fully tested before reaching the consumer.&nbsp;&nbsp; 

&nbsp;
 &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Having built up a decent market share in U.S., European and Middle Eastern markets, Jiu Ling plans on investing more effort on developing Central and South American markets. Though Jiu Ling is still considered to be a newcomer to the market, their potential for development should not be underestimated.]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Sports Supplier News ]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-07-07 15:22</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Technology and Innovation Ushered into the Sporting Goods Market to Offer New Vision to the World]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=205]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Taiwan sporting goods exports reached US$1,448,903,174 in 2010 which was a big rise compared to the US$1,130,670,371 in exports reported in 2009. This performance shows the global economy has recovere]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp;Taiwan sporting goods exports reached US$1,448,903,174 in 2010 which was a big rise compared to the US$1,130,670,371 in exports reported in 2009. This performance shows the global economy has recovered significantly. Export prospects are looking quite good for Taiwan sporting goods and more Taiwan companies are entering international markets to seek out good opportunities for sales growth.
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Among the sporting goods export categories in 2010, articles and equipment for general physical exercise, gymnastics or athletics occupied the top spot with exports of US$577,838,144 increasing by 42.79% over the same period last year. Exports of the second ranked category articles and equipment for other sports or outdoor games, not specifies or included elsewhere in this chapter; swimming pools and paddling poolstotaled US$283,458,946, growing by 14.94% over the same period. Other Golf equipment having exports reaching US$168,617,615 took third place and grew by 22.27%.
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The sporting goods categories that registered the highest growth in 2010 included sails of other textile materials, tables-table balls, and tables for table-tennis which recorded 10,200.41%, 868.75% and 450.00% growth respectively compared to 2009. Two categories: sailboards and other camping goods of cotton were the laggards of the group and recorded negative growth of -95.21% and -87.47% respectively.
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; As the global economy emerges from the financial storm, fitness and exercise has become an up and coming trend in emerging markets. As the U.S. and European economies continue to enjoy steady growth, the top five recipients of Taiwan sporting goods, the United States, Japan, Hong Kong, Germany and Great Britain, all grew by at least 10% which shows that Taiwan sporting goods are warmly welcomed by international markets. Total sporting goods exports in 2010 grew by 28% to reach the impressive figure of US$1.45 billion. Additionally, Taiwan has a competitive advantage in high-tech innovation which will help to further consolidate our position as a key supplier of sporting goods to the world.





]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201107/07/14-59-39-64-15.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Sports Supplier News ]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-07-07 14:52</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Tzy Shenq Enterprise Wins Customer Trust through Exceptional Design and Commitment to Quality]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=204]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Founded in 1976, Tzy Shenq Enterprise Co., Ltd. started out as a plastic mold developer. In response to subsequent market changes, the company decided to shift their focus over to the product design and manufacturing field. ]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[
Founded in 1976, Tzy Shenq Enterprise Co., Ltd. started out as a plastic mold developer. In response to subsequent market changes, the company decided to shift their focus over to the product design and manufacturing field. In operation for over 30 years, Tzy Shenq Enterprise has accumulated extensive experience in development, design and plastic injection molding &amp; assembly work. Drawing upon their all-in-one R&amp;D and production system and professional dedication to customer service, Tzy Shenq Enterprise has won broad customer recognition for its sports, recreational and agricultural tool products and successfully established a niche in export markets in Europe, U.S. and Japan which has made the company a leading developer and manufacturer of plastic injection molded products in Taiwan.&nbsp; 
&nbsp;
Tzy Shenq Enterprise is skilled at incorporating market thinking into product development. Careful product positioning and market analysis has been effective in raising product competitiveness. Standardized work processes not only simplify manufacturing processes and reduce costs but also help to enhance product R&amp;D capability and production efficiency. In the field of industrial and academic cooperation, Tzy Shenq Enterprise has entered into development projects with academic institutions to expand its product range as well as offer a greater product selection and OEM services to customers. 
&nbsp;
In addition to their professional R&amp;D capabilities, Tzy Shenq Enterprise has also invested large sums in manufacturing machinery and introduced precision instruments &amp; equipment. Through the use of CAE mold flow analysis, product design can be corrected in advance which reduces development risk and production costs as well as enabling the manufacture of precise and durable plastic injection molds. The company also has special processes for the injection molding of engineering plastic products. Through the use of material dehumidifying and drying equipment, mold temperature controllers and automated central supply systems, Tzy Shenq Enterprise can ensure that their injection molded products are high and stable quality.&nbsp; 
&nbsp;
Due to their strict product design requirements and rigorous attention paid to manufacturing equipment, Tzy Shenq Enterprise is able to accept business ranging for small plastic washers to engine covers for large construction machinery while providing customers with the very best service. In response to market challenges faced over the years, Tzy Shenq Enterprise has been awarded ISO 9001-2000, German TUV and Japanese JQA international certification so that the company can offer strict quality control and precise inspection and testing procedures to enable their products to pass a wide range of international inspection and quality standards.
&nbsp;
In the future, Tzy Shenq Enterprise will continue on developing new products and provide total product design and OEM services to customers in a variety of fields. By standing by their business philosophy of innovation, excellence, customer focus and honest business practices, the company has earned the trust of customers and put the company on a path to sustainable development.&nbsp;]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201106/16/10-59-44-45-13.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Sports Supplier News ]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[Pin Chuan Liu]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[William Hoyle]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-06-16 10:59</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Jiu Ling’s Innovative Chainless Recumbent Three-Wheel Bike Unlocks New Business Opportunities]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=203]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Established in 2008, Jiu Ling Co., Ltd. started out as a component, frame and paint OEM service provider. After having accumulated extensive experience and in-house mold making technology for over a decade, the company decided to launch their own brand three years ago and develop a line of recumbent]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[
Established in 2008, Jiu Ling Co., Ltd. started out as a component, frame and paint OEM service provider. After having accumulated extensive experience and in-house mold making technology for over a decade, the company decided to launch their own brand three years ago and develop a line of recumbent three-wheel bikes for recreational use. Jiu Ling chose to focus on one front wheel &ndash; two back wheel design. The advantages of a single front wheel design are shorter turning radius, better handling and greater agility. By equipping the bike with a large front wheel for faster speeds and smaller rear wheels to lower the center of gravity, the design is more stable and less likely to overturn. Its low frame design provides reduced wind resistance during pedaling and makes riding recumbent for long periods less fatiguing which provides greater safety and comfort.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 
&nbsp;Possessing many innovative designs and unique functions not available on other products, the main steering function is located at the back wheels to solve the steering difficulties experienced on three wheel bikes. This design makes it much easier to back up and even offers enjoyable bike drifting. The newly released model JIU-701 is foldable which makes it convenient to stow away. The bike also offers a one-of-a-kind chainless design which significantly reduces bike maintenance and effectively reduces the frame size. The eight-stage retractable mechanism with a 110 to 200 cm range can be adjusted to a level that optimally suits the height of rider so both children and adults can ride it safely.
&nbsp;Originally developed for exercise and recreational needs, Jiu Ling&rsquo;s recumbent three-wheel bikes also come with complete post-sales service and quality guarantee. From the thank-you letters received from customers, Jiu Ling discovered that their bikes helped kids develop a sense of balance and aided the rehabilitation of people with physical disabilities which has inadvertently created new niche markets for their products.&nbsp; 
&nbsp;Jiu Ling insists on offering the highest quality products that are both innovative and practical. By combining a structure that emphasizes safety and high-class aerodynamic styling, the bike offers an ergonomic design and lifestyle-friendly accessories. R&amp;D, design, manufacturing and shipping is done exclusively in Taiwan. Test riding is done by dedicated personnel and the R&amp;D team then performs three sets on testing on products. Welding, calibration, hardness testing and long-term load testing has all passed U.S. certification. Jiu Ling has always shown a strong commitment to ensure that their products are extensively and fully tested before reaching the consumer.&nbsp; &nbsp;
&nbsp;Having built up a decent market share in U.S., European and Middle Eastern markets, Jiu Ling plans on investing more effort on developing Central and South American markets. Though Jiu Ling is still considered to be a newcomer to the market, their potential for development should not be underestimated.&nbsp;]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201106/15/14-31-43-90-13.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Sports Supplier News ]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Noni ]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[William]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-06-15 14:22</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Y-T Industrial Specializes in the Development of Mats Made of Composite Materials, Yoga Mats and Other Foam Material Products]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=202]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Y-T Industrial has been a reputable manufacturer of foam material products for over 20 years. Originally, the company’s main products were athletic shoe soles, air pads and athletic shoe parts. ]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[Y-T Industrial has been a reputable manufacturer of foam material products for over 20 years. Originally, the company&rsquo;s main products were athletic shoe soles, air pads and athletic shoe parts. In recent years, Y-T Industrial has diversified its business by adding environmentally friendly yoga mats and EVA foam products to its product line. Y-T Industrial&rsquo;s business competency is being able to satisfy the different design requirements of a wide range of customers. In fact, the company is highly recognized in the industry for their first class products and competitive prices.&nbsp;
&nbsp;
In the field of shoe soles, Y-T Industrial specializes in the production of PU, EVA and PE material shoe soles. Their colors and styling are frequently updated to fully comply with market trends and requirements. PU is a flexible, impact resistant and highly&nbsp;comfortable material which can help reduce sports injury. EVA shoe soles can be designed for different levels of hardness which can improve foot support. PE is a lightweight material which makes them suitable for skates and skateboard shoes.&nbsp;
&nbsp;
Y-T Industrial has also invested a great deal of effort into the development of composite material shoe soles. One example is combining the flexibility of PU with the support features of EVA to give a single pair of shoes both solid support and flexibility. The company is able to manufacture shoe shoes that offer comfort, shock absorption, breathability, odor and mildew resistance, firm support, diverse styling using a variety of materials. At present, the company is working with famous American athletic shoe maker to manufacture shoe soles for basketball, skateboard and golf shoes.
&nbsp;
As for their yoga mats, Y-T Industrial primarily uses environmental friendly materials that do not contain PVC and eight heavy metals. During the manufacturing process, only non-toxic adhesives are used. Therefore, their products can be exported to countries in North America and Europe where there are strict environmental protection standards. Their specifications, dimensions, thickness and color all meet customer design and manufacturing requirements. The company offers dual color mats that can used on both their front and back sides. A variety of patterns are also available. Consumers in Europe and the US especially appreciate their mats for their slip-resistance, attractive appearance and utility. &nbsp;
&nbsp;
Y-T Industrial&rsquo;s corporate culture is based on quality first and customer first. Possessing precision production and quality controls, the company strives to create high quality products that are marketed through the Internet, media and international shows. In the future, Y-T Industrial hopes to introduce even more exceptional products to the world and successfully broaden their presence in international markets.&nbsp;
&nbsp;]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201105/27/17-42-15-89-13.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Sports Supplier News ]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[Ellen Chang]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[William Hoyle]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-05-27 17:34</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Karting Clutch BiJump]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=201]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Union Material Co., Ltd., located in Taiwan, is originally major in designing,formulating and manufacturing self-lubricated elements for various industrial mechanisms such as bushings for bicycles/motorcycles]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[Union Material Co., Ltd., located in Taiwan, is originally major in designing,formulating and manufacturing self-lubricated elements for various industrial mechanisms such as bushings for bicycles/motorcycles; sliding bushings for business machines; journal bushings for athletic equipments and many mechanical sliding/ rolling elements required to have properties of low noise, low wear,self-lubrication and long durability.
&nbsp;
Since the self-lubricated elements from UM have excellent tribological properties and reasonable price so these parts are not only adopted by most domestic companies but also exported to China, Europe,Japan and United States.
&nbsp;
In addition to the business of self-lubricated elements,Union Material takes the advantage of their innovative ability in material formulation and structural designing.Now they have extended their business into designing/manufacturing functional transmission parts for CVT vehicles and they have become an OEM supplier to provide various roller weights to many well known Scooter/ATV/Buggy makers in China, Japan and Taiwan.
&nbsp;
Moreover, UM have created their own brand, Dr.Pulley&reg; to promote their tuning product series ,particularly the patented Sliding Roller Weight ( US 7 276 004 ) and HiT clutch ( JP 3134915 ), to the world-wide aftermarket and have earned a high reputation for themselves.
&nbsp;
According the spokesman of UM, they&rsquo;re now developing a high performance clutch (BiJump &reg; ) for karting,and this special clutch will be able to efficiently transmit the engine power directly from the engine crank to the ground and this performance will be obviously shown at roundabout of racing track.]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201105/05/16-44-51-21-13.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Motorcycle Supplier News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Union Material Co.,Ltd.]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-05-05 13:54</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Always Putting the Customer and Service First, Prohi Sports – the Sporting Goods Specialist]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=200]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[PROHI SPORTS was established in 2002, and it located at JingHai Economic Development Area in Tianjin China, and specializes in manufacture a extensive range of sporting nets and sporting goods.]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[PROHI SPORTS was established in 2002, and it located at JingHai Economic Development Area in Tianjin China, and specializes in manufacture a extensive range of sporting nets and sporting goods. &nbsp;&nbsp;
&nbsp;
With years of experience, advanced equipment and strictly quality control, our products are well received and all exported to the overseas market. &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;
&nbsp;
We believe that quality is life, so we make every effort to explore new designs and to satisfy the customer&rsquo;s needs. At the same time, we take great care to ensure that the requirements are fully understood and your expectation met with the highly effective solutions.
&nbsp;
We have high caliber personnel, sophisticated engineering and R&amp;D team, experienced and skillful workers and sound quality control system. By that we can control our costs better and our prices and competitive.
&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;
We have worldwide US10 million coverage of PLI on our trampoline, and we also have after sale service agent in the worldwide.
&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;
Prohi Sports&rsquo; very confident that we can challenge all kinds of difficulties, the requests of customers is the benchmark which can drive us to do perfectly in the future. In line with the standards：Customer First, Service First and we never stop to improve our product quality and designs so to offer customers the most satisfactory sporting goods. Our goal is to expand our markets worldwide, and we will continue to work harder for tomorrow.
&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;
We sincerely hope that we, together with all the customers, old and new, will develop greatly and build a brighter future.
&nbsp;

    
        
            
        
    

]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201104/28/14-04-12-66-13.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Sports Supplier News ]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[Tung Shrim Enterprise Co., Ltd.]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-04-20 13:56</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[ATV Exports Recover in 2010  Strong Demand Seen in Emerging Markets]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=199]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[According to statistics from Taiwan’s Directorate General of Customs, exports of Taiwan ATV (all-terrain vehicles) in 2010 reached US$199,997,000 dollars rising by 13.88% over the US$175,619,000 reported in the previous year. ]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[According to statistics from Taiwan&rsquo;s Directorate General of Customs, exports of Taiwan ATV (all-terrain vehicles) in 2010 reached US$199,997,000 dollars rising by 13.88% over the US$175,619,000 reported in the previous year.&nbsp;
&nbsp;
Looking at the top three recipients of Taiwan ATV exports, the United States was the number one Taiwan ATV importer receiving US$44,104,000 in exports followed by Germany and France who took in US$35,964,000 and US$23,409,000 in Taiwan ATV exports respectively. Other countries in the top ten were Belgium, Italy, Sweden and Canada. There were only a few countries in the top ten, Australia, Saudi Arabia and South Korea, that were located outside of Europe and North America.&nbsp;
&nbsp;
Compared to the statistics compiled from the previous year, we can see there were a few strong performers among the top 20 countries such as Russia, Australia, Finland and the UAE. Russia has the highest growth rate with 92.66%. The other countries also had vigorous growth rates of 66.80%, 56.39% and 54.00% which shows there is strong potential for growth in emerging markets and certain European countries.&nbsp;
&nbsp;
Due to the economic recovery in Europe and North America markets in 2010, Taiwanese manufacturers received quite a few more orders than the previous year. As the ATV market continues to heat up, Taiwan manufacturers will need to not only continue to produce high quality and high value-added products to achieve market segmentation goals, resources from R&amp;D, manufacturing, suppliers and distributors must be brought together through industry alliances to respond to changing market trends &amp; low price competition and open up a blue ocean of market space for Taiwan&rsquo;s ATV industry.
[pagebreak]
]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201104/18/14-56-06-88-13.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Industry News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[Pin-Chuan Liu ]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[William Hoyle]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-04-18 14:53</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[FORSA- Professional Manufacturer of Shock Absorbers for ATVs]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=198]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[FORSA Enterprises Co., Ltd., was set up on the 16th of August 1987. We are specialized in shock absorbers for motorcycles and special vehicles. We not only offer OEM service for domestic and oversea vehicle assembly factories but also export the products to over 50 countries.]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[FORSA Enterprises Co., Ltd., was set up on the 16th of August 1987. We are specialized in shock absorbers for motorcycles and special vehicles. We not only offer OEM service for domestic and oversea vehicle assembly factories but also export the products to over 50 countries.
&nbsp;
The first shock absorber for ATV was produced by FORSA and 80% of Taiwan&rsquo;s ATV shock absorbers are also supplied by FORSA ; Honesty, trust, diligence, frugality, and the pursuit for perfection are our business principles. We have always been improving ourselves constantly and developing new models with high quality and competitive prices.
&nbsp;
FORSA has a highly automated production plant in southern Taiwan. The plant is equipped with the most advanced production equipment and testing instruments; In 1997, we moved to our present factory and expanded new inspecting instruments in order to meet customer's quality and quantity requirement. Moreover, we also expanded a whole set of CNC equipment to our production line in 1998. Despite the economic downturn, sales at FORSA over the past decade have increased at an annual rate of 10% or more.
&nbsp;
We now manufacture over 2000 kinds of shock absorbers and obtained ISO9001 certification confirmed by British organization SGS. We sincerely welcome inquiries from every potential customers as well as technological cooperation.


    
        
            
            
        
    



]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201104/18/14-36-19-18-13.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Motorcycle Supplier News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[Forsa]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[Forsa]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-04-13 14:24</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[KYMCO Goes International with their “Better than Best” Spirit]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=197]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Going international with their “Better than Best” business motto and highly professional management team, KYMCO always stays focused on the customer at every stage of their business including product development, sales service, part supply and marketing network. This has enabled KYMCO to become the ]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[Going international with their &ldquo;Better than Best&rdquo; business motto and highly professional management team, KYMCO always stays focused on the customer at every stage of their business including product development, sales service, part supply and marketing network. This has enabled KYMCO to become the brand of choice for consumers in Taiwan and abroad.
&nbsp;
KYMCO has steadily expanded their presence in overseas markets since making their international debut in 1979.This solid export performance has made the company a trailblazer in Taiwan&rsquo;s motorcycle industry. After starting to market their products internationally under the KYMCO brand in 1989, the company continued to dedicate themselves to motorcycle research and development but also looked to become a recognized player in the ATV, mobility scooters and general purpose engine segments. With their global sales network encompassing 90 countries in Asia, Africa, Europe and the Americas, KYMCO has already built up a significant market share in European countries, becoming one the most popular import brands there.
&nbsp;
KYMCO has set up a network of highly accessible sales service centers in Taiwan and around the world. The company has consistently been a leader in the motorcycle industry. In addition to being top selling motorcycle brand in Taiwan for seven consecutive years, KYMCO also earned Taiwan&rsquo;s Outstanding Export Performance Award and was rated the number one brand among European distributors in a poll conducted by a French motorcycle magazine. A French professional motorcycle magazine chose KYMCO as the number one brand in France. Another French trade magazine rated KYMCO&rsquo;s KXR 250, &nbsp;Mxer 150 and Grand Dink 125 scooters as the top selling products in the market. KYMCO&rsquo;s MXU 150/250 was also selected as the best leisure and utility ATV in a German professional magazine. In addition, KYMCO was given the Outstanding Corporation Award in Spain and named one of the Top 100 Influential Corporations in America. No matter where you go, you can see the sleek shapes of KYMCO motorcycles crisscrossing city streets. Regardless of what country you are in, KYMCO stays dedicated and true to their customers.
&nbsp;
On their path to building a global business, KYMCO&rsquo;s exceptional R&amp;D team has worked to unveil stunning new products at Munich and Milan shows to expand into overseas markets. KYMCO was also the only Taiwanese motorcycle manufacturer to attend the Tokyo Motor Show. KYMCO motorcycle and power-assisted products have turned heads at international shows with their bold styling, outstanding performance and advanced technology. By standing out at international venues, KYMCO has not just become a model for companies in Taiwan but also set an example of how to build a successful world leading brand.
&nbsp;]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201104/18/14-02-38-81-13.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Motorcycle Supplier News]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[kymco]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[William Hoyle]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-04-13 13:59</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Deng Shuenn Finds International Success with their Core Expertise in Motor Technology]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=88]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Deng Shuenn Industrial Co., Ltd, established in 1988, specializes in the manufacture of sporting goods and massage equipment such as vibration machines, swing machines, beauty massagers and indoor exercise bikes.]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[
Deng Shuenn Industrial Co., Ltd, established in 1988, specializes in the manufacture of sporting equipment and massage equipment such as oscillating vibtations, vibration machines, Chi machines, beauty massagers and workout bikes. The main overseas markets are presently in Europe, followed by the United States. Besides offering OEM service, Deng Shuenn has been working to provide more advanced ODM capabilities and customer customization services.
&nbsp;
Compared to other companies in their industry, Deng Shuenn&rsquo;s chief advantage is their core competency in motor technology and mechanical structural design. For their vibration machine, their most popular product on the market, the internal motor and mechanical structure design has been awarded patents from a number of companies. Featuring outstanding technology that leads the industry, it has won rave reviews for customers in markets all over the world. Chairman Huang Yu-tong has been in the motor component business for decades so he possesses a wealth of expertise in motor parts and components. In the years afterwards, he accumulated nearly 30 years of experience in motor assembly and motor related product manufacturing. Armed with this broad range of experience, Chairman Huang has not only established production processes for Deng Shuenn that fully control product quality but also the ability to research and develop innovative new products through his deep knowledge of motors.
&nbsp;
&ldquo;How to make products which are good quality, affordable and energy saving is what we care most about. Letting customer spend less money and enjoy higher added value is our mission,&rdquo; said Deng Shuenn Sales Manager. To achieve this goal, Deng Shuenn continually introduces products with enhanced power saving and safety features. The company has also entered into cross-industry alliances to roll out other innovative products such as dual exercise bike for elderly that offers medical rehabilitation therapy-like functions and climber that offers a mountain climbing experience at home to satisfy the ever expanding requirements of the senior citizen market. &nbsp;
&nbsp;
Because of the strict quality control concepts that he learned early on from Japanese practices, Deng Shuenn&rsquo;s products are well known for their excellent quality in both international and domestic markets. Safety is also a top priority for any motor-powered equipment. Using poor quality motors just to save money can lead to tragic accidents and cause irreparable harm to one&rsquo;s business reputation. As a specialist in motors, Deng Shuenn offers stable quality products at reasonable prices. Looking towards the future, the company plans to adopt a market segmentation strategy and design products that closely conforms to the requirements of each age group.&nbsp;
&nbsp;

    
        
            
        
    
]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201104/18/11-02-01-77-13.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[sport]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Sports Supplier News ]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[Tsai Wang chun]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[William Hoyle]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-04-11 17:01</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[Always Green and Innovative, Lian-Hang Health-Tech Brings Affordable and Highly Functional TFT to the World]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/news/show.php?itemid=112]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[Strongly dedicated to offering green and innovative products, Lian-Hang Health-Tech Co., Ltd specializes in the manufacture of fitness exercise mechatronic systems including exercise computers, generators and auto lubrication devices.]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[
Strongly dedicated to offering green and innovative products, Lian-Hang Health-Tech Co., Ltd specializes in the manufacture of fitness exercise mechatronic systems including exercise computers, generators and auto lubrication devices. In recent years, the company has successfully developed and manufactured TFT touch panel displays, fine quality devices at highly competitive products ready for full introduction into the fitness equipment market.

In the past, TFT displays could not be used in many applications because they were prohibitively expensive. Always advancing at the cutting edge of technology, Lian-Hang Health-Tech took the lead to integrate TFT technology into the fitness industry. The company developed a top quality and affordably priced TFT for incorporation into treadmills and other fitness equipment. The ergonomically designed touch panel screen features USB transmission and movie viewing, audio-visual and picture frame entertainment functions. Data like weight and exercise time can be entered into the device to precisely calculate the exercise amount to assist in individual health management and planning making it a technology product that conforms to global trends.&nbsp;

Lian-Hang Health-Tech is made up of a team of engineers with extensive professional backgrounds. In the early days, the company developed the capability to provide effective custom technological solutions its customers. Having built up a strong reputation for quality and technical expertise, Lian-Hang Health-Tech has a clear competitive advantage in the industry. In a short period of time, the company has been able to develop and manufacture close to twenty patented products and the number continues to grow. Now, the company closely cooperates with a number of domestic manufacturers and well-established customers in the U.S., Brazil and Canada. In the future, Lian-Hang Health-Tech plans to establish a trading company in China to develop the domestic market there.&nbsp;

Besides TFT, Lian-Hang Health-Tech was the first company in Taiwan to develop an indoor bicycle generator with a specially designed charging device that can charge mobile phones and batteries. It is not only convenient to users and environmentally friendly. It enjoys tax breaks in some European countries because it is classified as a self-generating product.&nbsp;
&nbsp;

    
        
            
            
        
    

Lian-Hang Health-Tech President Frank Hsu said TFT displays and indoor bicycle generators have been the company&rsquo;s representative products. Based upon customer response to our products and the increasing number of new customers, Lian-Hang Health-Tech expects to see significant growth this year. With regard to future developments, President Hsu also mentioned that the company also sees growth potential in the bicycle market. New products such as bicycle generators and anti-theft alarms are now in the works. Standing by their business philosophy of &ldquo;advancing at the cutting edge of the industry to offer innovative and new value products&rdquo;, Lian-Hang Health-Tech is fully prepared to offer novel solutions to a wide range of customer requirements.


    
        
            
        
    
]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/file/upload/201002/05/16-08-28-35-13.jpg]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[sports|meter|sport]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[Sports Supplier News ]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[Ho Shao-ying]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[William Hoyle]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-03-25 16:09</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[公司介紹(About Us)的設定]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/help/show.php?itemid=17]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;依照以下步驟操作，您將可在自己的公司網站(About Us區域)，呈現公司簡介。
&nbsp;
1.登入會員商務中心(member.imb2b.com)
&nbsp;
2.登入後，請點選資料管理&nbsp;
&nbsp;

&nbsp;
3.進入資料管理後，請點選公司介紹
&nbsp;
4.進入公司介紹後，請直接在編輯區域填入公司簡介即可。

(請注意：該區域僅能輸入英文文字內容，若放置圖片，將影響貴公司網站首頁和About Us頁面的呈現效果。)]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[About Us]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[聯絡人與公司資料]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-03-18 10:25</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[產品圖片跑馬燈(Hot Products)的設定]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/help/show.php?itemid=16]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp;依照以下操作步驟，您將可在自己的公司網站Hot Products區域，呈現產品跑馬燈效果。
&nbsp;
1.登入會員商務中心(member.imb2b.com) 。
&nbsp;
2.登入後，點選左側導覽列的訊息管理。
&nbsp;
3.點選供應管理。
&nbsp;
4.進入供應管理後，選擇欲出現跑馬燈效果的產品，並點擊修改按鈕。
&nbsp;
5.進入該產品修改頁面後，請移至網頁最下方的&quot;我的網站推薦&quot;，並點選&quot;是&quot;。
&nbsp;


6.點擊&quot;送出&quot;。屆時該產品圖片將會在貴公司的網站首頁Hot Products區域出現跑馬燈效果。]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[Hot Products]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[供應工具]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-03-17 16:25</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[分類項目(Category)的設定]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/help/show.php?itemid=15]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;依照以下操作步驟，您將可在自己的公司網站中，利用產品類別(Category)，管理公司產品。

1.登入會員商務中心(member.imb2b.com) 。
&nbsp;
2.登入後，點選左側導覽列的訊息管理。
&nbsp;
3.點選供應管理。
&nbsp;
4.進入供應管理後，請點選供應分類，屆時系統將直接進入產品分類。
&nbsp;
5.進入產品分類後，您將可自訂分類名稱與排序，並藉由自訂分類來管理您的公司產品。
&nbsp;
6.完成產品分類後，請再點選左側訊息管理中的供應管理，屆時您將可在已發佈的產品清單中進行類別修改。
&nbsp;
7.請在產品清單中，點擊修改按鈕，進入該產品修改頁面後，請移至網頁最下方的自定義分類，選擇該產品是屬於哪個分類項目。
&nbsp;
8.設定完畢後，點擊&quot;送出&quot;。屆時在貴公司網站的Category中，就會顯示您所新增的分類項目，並可在該分類中找到所有相關產品。]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[Category]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[供應工具]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-03-17 16:14</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[公司新聞(News Center)的發佈]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/help/show.php?itemid=14]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp;依照以下操作步驟，您將可在自己的公司網站中發佈新聞訊息。

1.登入會員商務中心(member.imb2b.com)

2.登入後，點選左邊導覽列的網站管理選項

3.點選公司新聞選項

4.點選新增新聞，進行新聞訊息發佈，點擊&rdquo;確定&rdquo;後，即可產生News Center的新聞內容。]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[News Center]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[網站設置]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-03-17 16:02</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[多項產品一次比較]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/help/show.php?itemid=13]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[如果您需要將同一分類的或您感興趣的多項產品，進行一次性的列表比較，建議您可以使用產品比較的操作。

本功能僅在產品頻道區的首頁、列表頁及搜尋頁能使用，首頁或其他頻道區則無此項功能。以下為操作步驟：

1. 勾選欲比較或感興趣的產品，超個二項以上（包含二項）時會自動觸發產品比較／詢問的對話框，點擊對話框上的「Compare(比較)」。

2. 隨即進入產品比較頁面，以列表比較方式顯示所勾選的產品項目。透過比較之後，使用者也可以利用列表訊息最下方的「Inquiry(詢問)」的按鈕，傳送詢問函給屬意的產品供應者。

(以下待續)]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[compare]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[產品比較]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-02-21 17:01</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[使用關鍵字搜尋產品供應者]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/help/show.php?itemid=12]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[如果您正在尋找如何使用關鍵字搜尋產品訊息的幫助說明，建議您可以參考關鍵字搜尋一文。

在公司(Company)頻道區的環境下，使用者可以輕易地在首尾導覽列／頁尾搜尋列找到關鍵字輸入框，搜尋產品供應者的操作步驟如下：

1. 請將您有興趣搜尋的關鍵字鍵入頁首或頁尾的關鍵字輸入框裡，關鍵字可以是產品關鍵字，亦可以是公司名稱的局部等。

2. 按下放大鏡圖示／Search按鈕以完成搜尋。

3. 檢視搜尋結果頁面下方，是否有任何搜尋結果記錄。如果完全沒有或者稀少零星記錄的話，建議您應該選擇更通用的關鍵字來搜尋，以擴大搜尋結果範圍；如果搜尋結果的記錄過多時，也建議您應該使用更專門的關鍵字來搜尋，以縮小搜尋結果範圍。

如果您想要瞭解更多關於本網站所提供的智能搜尋功能，建議您可以參考智能搜尋功能一文。]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[search company]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[搜尋賣家(公司)]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-02-21 11:30</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[使用「進階搜尋工具」搜尋產品]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/help/show.php?itemid=10]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[
當使用者想要搜尋供應產品時，除了使用頁首／頁尾的「一般搜尋工具」，輸入關鍵字搜尋外，ImB2B網站也提供「進階搜尋工具」，讓資料取得更迅速有效率。
&nbsp;
進階搜尋工具，提供更多自定義選項與關鍵字輸入，讓使用者能更精準搜尋所需產品／其他資訊；透過頻道區下拉式選單的切換，您隨時都可在不同頻道區內，使用進階搜尋工具。以下就以最常用的產品頻道區進階搜尋工具為例，提供操作步驟以供參考：
&nbsp;
1. 在網頁導覽列的搜尋工具框旁，按下「Advanced」按鈕。或者，在一般搜尋工具輸入任何關鍵字，無論是否找到結果記錄，皆會進入進階搜尋工具的頁面。
&nbsp;
2. 每一頻道區的進階搜尋工具裡，系統提供的自定義選項或輸入值皆有相異。以產品頻道區而言，提供七個選項，皆可全選／填，亦可僅選／填一項，當選／填的資料愈多，搜尋範圍愈窄，以下逐項說明：
&nbsp;
2.1 在「Keyword」欄位，您可以輸入欲搜尋產品的關鍵字，建議以英文詞彙為主；除了部份頻道區為繁體中文頁面，才允許以繁體中文語彙進行搜尋。關鍵字欄位提供六種比對模式，預設值為「模糊」比對模式。以下說明六種模式之間的差異：
&nbsp;
2.1.1 模糊比對：係針對每則產品訊息的「產品名稱」欄位值進行比對。惟搜尋結果會因輸入的產品名稱差異而有所不同。
&nbsp;
2.1.2 標題比對：係針對每則產品訊息的「產品標題」欄位值進行比對。搜尋結果可能因標題欄位可容納的字元較多，而比前者搜尋效果佳。
&nbsp;
2.1.3 全文比對：係針對每則產品訊息的「產品名稱」、「產品標題」、「詳細說明」等所有欄位值進行比對。全文比對是最精準的搜尋比對模式。
&nbsp;
2.1.4 簡介比對：係經由系統以自動摘要方式截取每則產品訊息的「詳細說明」欄位進行比對。對於想搜尋某項產品細節描述的使用者，建議可以此種方式進行比對。
&nbsp;
2.1.5 公司比對：係針對每則產品訊息的供應者（公司名稱）欄位進行比對。在一些情況下，使用者可能不記得產品名稱或產品細節，僅知道提供產品的公司名稱，或是想知道某一公司所發佈的產品訊息時，建議可以此種方式進行比對。
&nbsp;
2.1.6 品牌比對：係針對每則產品訊息的「產品品牌」欄位進行比對。
&nbsp;
2.2 在「Category」欄位，您可以選擇想要搜尋產品的所屬產業分類及子分類，藉以縮小搜尋範圍。惟搜尋結果受限於產品供應者對於產品分類歸屬不同而有所差異。
&nbsp;
2.3 在「Location」欄位，您可以選擇想要搜尋產品供應者的所在地區，除非有特定搜尋需求，一般情況不建議使用該自定義欄位。
&nbsp;
2.4 在「Updated Date」欄位，您可藉由滑鼠點擊文字欄位，或按下行事曆圖示選擇日期，由此選擇起訖時間，系統將會比對出指定期間內的資料搜尋結果。
&nbsp;
2.5&nbsp;在「Type」欄位，提供「產品產地」、「標價與否」、「帶有圖片與否」等，使用者可以依據搜尋需求自行選擇。

2.6 在「Price」欄位，提供使用者可以填寫最小金額、最大金額的標價範圍，兩者皆可填寫，單獨填寫亦可；此一欄位與2.5的price勾選的區別，係2.5的price勾選值，如果勾選的話，則會搜尋所有帶有價標的產品訊息，而此欄位的填寫值，則提供使用者更精確的價標搜尋，兩個部份即使同時使用也無大礙。對於想使用產品價格來搜尋產品的使用者，建議可以合理地使用本欄位，惟搜尋結果受限於產品供應者未必提供商品價格。

2.7 在「Sort by」欄位，提供使用者10種排序方式，如果不選擇的話，則系統以預設排序方式自動排列您的搜尋結果；如果您有特定的排序需求，請依照下拉式選單選擇所需的排序方式。

2.8 最後，確認所有自定義欄位值之後，按下「Search」進行搜尋。如果您想重新設定自定義值，也可以按下「Reset」重設新的搜尋。

如果搜尋結果過少或幾乎沒有的話，建議放寬關鍵字／分類／更新時間／價格等的欄位值範圍；搜尋結果過多的話，建議縮小關鍵字／分類／更新時間／價格等的欄位值範圍。有時候，參考別人都在找什麼產品或關鍵字，也不失為一個好辦法，建議您也可以閱讀熱門關鍵字一文。

如果您想要瞭解更多關於本網站所提供的智能搜尋功能，建議您可以參考智能搜尋功能一文。
&nbsp;
]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[search advanced]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[搜尋供應產品]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-02-18 15:35</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[使用關鍵字搜尋產品]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/help/show.php?itemid=11]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[ImB2B網站提供了完整且醒目的搜尋工具，提供使用者進行最直接且有效的搜尋操作。

在網站每一頁面的頁首和頁尾，皆有一處關鍵字搜尋輸入框，並視頁面所在頻道區域不同而自動調整。首頁及產品的頻道區域，皆自動預設為Product。搜尋產品的操作步驟如下：

1. 首頁或產品頻道區的頁首導覽列搜尋工具／頁尾搜尋工具，輸入您想要搜尋的產品關鍵字，如motorcycle等。

2. 按下放大鏡圖示／Search按鈕以完成搜尋。

3. 檢視搜尋結果頁面下方，是否有任何產品訊息記錄。如果完全沒有或者稀少零星記錄的話，建議您應該選擇更通用的關鍵字來搜尋，以擴大搜尋結果範圍；如果搜尋產品的記錄過多時，也建議您應該使用更專門的關鍵字來搜尋，以縮小搜尋結果範圍。


如果您想要更精準地搜尋網站產品或其他資訊，建議您可以參考進階搜尋工具一文。
如果您想要瞭解更多關於本網站所提供的智能搜尋功能，建議您可以參考智能搜尋功能一文。]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[搜尋供應產品]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-02-18 14:40</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[會員資料管理(公司資料)]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/help/show.php?itemid=8]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[請在商務中心(My ImB2B)歡迎列右上方，點擊「資料管理」後進行以下的步驟操作。

公司資料的會員管理，可區分為三個部份：公司資料、公司聯絡方式、公司介紹。

1.「公司資料」部份，除了英文公司名稱不可隨意變更之外，其他欄位如公司類型、形象圖片等皆可以視情況隨時變更。

1.1 勾選公司類型，最多可以勾選4個。(必填)

1.2 透過[上傳][預覽][刪除]等操作，發佈公司的形象圖片。建議使用LOGO、辦公環境等標誌性圖片，最佳顯示大小為寬度180px，高度180px。

1.3 選擇公司所在的地區。(必填)

1.4 透過[搜尋][新增][刪除]等操作，選擇公司的主要經營產業，最多可以選擇6個產業項目。(必填)

1.5 視公司事實狀態填寫公司的主要經營項目，建議免費會員在沒有SEO工具的條件下，儘可能將公司的關鍵字填寫於此欄位，將有助於Google等搜尋引摰的收錄。(必填)

1.6 視公司事實狀態填寫公司的成立年份，以西元年份四碼數值輸入。(必填)

1.7 視公司經營國際市場現況，勾選適合的經營市場，最多可以勾選4個。(必填)

1.8 視公司事實狀態選擇公司規模。建議選填此欄位，將有助於有限條件下獲得國際買主的青睞。

1.9 視公司事實狀態填寫註冊資料額，以美元計算。建議選填此欄位，將有助於有限條件下獲得國際買主的青睞。

1.10 視公司事實狀態填寫「銷售的服務(提供的服務)」「採購的產品(需要的服務)」。

1.11 按下「修改」按鈕，完成此部份的更新。

2.「公司聯繫方式」部份，為公司對外的聯繫管道，此部份的完整度將可能直接或間接影響國際買主的詢問程度，請依公司事實狀態誠實且正確填寫以下資料：

2.1 在「主要經營地址」欄位，請填寫公司英文地址；如果公司地址有多處，請以總公司或辦公室地址為主。(必填)

2.2 在「郵遞區號」欄位，請依據2.1欄位填寫。依據中華郵政公司的規範，建議填寫此欄位。

2.3 在「公司電話」欄位，請依照國碼-區碼-電話號碼的方式填寫該公司電話號碼。建議填寫公司的代表電話號碼。(必填)

2.4 在「公司傳真」欄位，請依照2.3輸入格式填寫該公司傳真號碼。

2.5 在「公司Email」欄位，請輸入該公司對外公開的Email地址，如：可以為業務部、國外部等Email地址，建議與註冊用Email地址使用不相同的地址。

2.6 在「公司網址」欄位，請輸入該公司的網址名稱，在開頭請加上http://。

2.7 按下「修改」按鈕，完成此部份的更新。

3.「公司介紹」部份，請依據公司事實狀態誠實且正確地填寫公司簡介描述。

3.1 建議可以參考公司經營方向、得獎記錄、規劃願景等角度切入撰寫「公司介紹」。(必填)

3.2 按下「修改」部份，完成此部份的更新。


    如果您在註冊後第一次登入ImB2B網站，系統會在商務中心(My ImB2B)首頁以黃色醒目字條的方式，提醒該帳戶會員您必須完成聯絡人及公司資料等必填欄位項目後，方可使用本網站所提供的優質服務(如：發佈產品訊息等)。


    ImB2B網站係以國際貿易商務平台為經營目標，以美式英文為網站預設語言，本站主要的欄位輸入請以英文進行填寫或核選。
]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[register]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[編輯/修改會員資料]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-02-17 16:10</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[會員資料管理(聯絡人資料)]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/help/show.php?itemid=7]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[請在商務中心(My ImB2B)歡迎列右上方，點擊「資料管理」後進行以下的步驟操作。

聯絡人資料的會員管理，可區分為兩個部份：個人資料、密碼管理。

1.「個人資料」部份，除了會員名稱、註冊用Email地址不可隨意變更之外，其他欄位如職位、部門等皆可以視情況隨時變更。

1.1 填寫聯絡人姓名，前者為英文名字，後者為英文姓氏。(必填)

1.2 核選聯絡人性別。(必填)

1.3 視情況填寫手機號碼。(若欲使用本網站手機簡訊功能時，則此欄位必欄)

1.4 視情況填寫所屬公司部門名稱。

1.5 視情況填寫所屬職位名稱。

1.6 視情況填寫有效聯絡人或公司MSN的Email地址。

1.7 視情況填寫有效聯絡人或公司Skype帳號名稱。

2.「密碼管理」部份，在安全性考量下，建議定期進行帳戶密碼變更是最有效、也最安全的做法。

ImB2B網站上所謂的「密碼」，嚴格來說，可以區分為兩種：帳戶密碼和支付密碼。可以透過此部份的操作，進行該密碼的變更，兩者的操作非常相似。以下就以帳戶密碼的操作為例：

2.1 在「現有密碼」欄位，輸入目前帳戶登入密碼。

2.2 在「新的登錄密碼」欄位，請輸入欲更改的新帳戶密碼。如果該欄位保持空白，系統視為不變更密碼。

2.3 在「重覆新密碼」欄位，請再次輸入2.2所填寫的新帳戶密碼。兩者必須完全相同，英文字母大小寫是相異的。

2.4 按下「修改」按鈕，即可立即變更密碼。支付密碼的變更步驟，請參考帳戶密碼的變更方式。


如果您忘了帳戶登入密碼，請參考找回密碼一文。
如果您密碼的安全性有疑惑的話，請參考密碼強度一文。]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[password payment]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[編輯/修改會員資料]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-02-17 14:46</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[使用「密碼管理」來修改密碼]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://www.imb2b.com/help_tw/show.php?itemid=7#password]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[&nbsp;]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[修改密碼]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-02-17 14:01</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[找回密碼]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/help/show.php?itemid=6]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[人似乎不總是那麼完美的。當您不小心忘記帳戶登入密碼，以致無法順利地登入ImB2B網站，享受本網站的各項優質服務時，請進行找回密碼的動作

1. 在登入頁面的登入框右上方，點擊「Forgot Password」連結按鈕

2. 進入找回密碼頁面，依序輸入用戶名、註冊Email、新登錄密碼、重覆密碼等

3. 按下「下一步」之後，ImB2B網站系統會自動寄送一封驗證郵件至第2步驟的註冊Email裡，開啟該封信件，點擊信件內容的超連結完成找回密碼。]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[password]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[忘記密碼]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-02-09 17:32</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[會員登出]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/help/show.php?itemid=5]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[在非個人或公用電腦的使用環境下，建議會員在確認結束操作後，應進行登出的動作。

如果您之前成功登入的話，ImB2B網站會在歡迎列顯示帳戶聯絡人名字，及登出Logout的超連結路徑。

點擊「Logout」後，即可立刻登出該會員帳戶。]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[login logout]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[會員登入]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-02-09 17:12</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[會員登入]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/help/show.php?itemid=4]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[您可能訪問了一個需要登入的頁面，或是使用本網站所提供的功能服務時，需先進行登入的動作。

ImB2B網站有兩個可以提供登入的超連結路徑，一個在歡迎列上的Login，另一個則在首頁的會員登入框處。

1. 點擊Login進入登入頁面後，依序輸入使用者名稱及密碼，按下「登錄」 完成登入動作。
註：登入成功後，網頁上方的歡迎列會發生改變，顯示帳戶聯絡人名稱及登出連結等。

2. 在ImB2B首頁的會員登入框，依序輸入使用者名稱及密碼，即可快速完成登入。

]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[login]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[會員登入]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-02-09 16:49</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[會員註冊]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://demo.imb2b.com/help/show.php?itemid=3]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[依照以下步驟操作，您可以輕鬆成為ImB2B免費會員，立即開啟商務之旅。

1.ImB2B網站提供2個註冊的連結按鈕，一個在歡迎列上的Join Free，另一個則在首頁的會員登入框的Join Free! Sign Up Now...

2.進入註冊頁面後，依序填寫帳戶、聯絡人、公司資訊：

2.1 填寫帳戶資訊(Account Information)

2.2 填寫聯絡人資訊(Contact Information)

2.3 填寫公司資訊(Company Information)

3. 填寫驗證問題、驗證碼

4. 閱讀服務條款之後，按下「同意服務條款並送出」按鈕，結束註冊頁面，此時ImB2B網站系統將會提醒啟動認證機制。(會員身份為待審核會員)

5. ImB2B網站系統會自動寄發一封認證信至貴司(即在2.2聯絡人資訊中所填入的電子郵件帳號)的電子郵件信箱，您只需要開啟會員啟用認證信，按下信件內的超連結，就可正式成為ImB2B網站的免費會員。]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[register]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[會員申請與服務]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2011-02-09 15:23</pubDate>
</item>
</document>